[
  {
    id: 1,
    name: "Ürün 1",
    category: "Elektronik",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 2079.51,
    brand: "Marka A",
    stock: 21,
    ratings: {
      average: 1.3,
      count: 153,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "APS-C",
      resolution: "23MP",
      videoResolution: "8K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: true,
        bluetooth: false,
        gps: false,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "Li-ion",
        life: "450 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "375g",
        dimensions: "134 x 88 x 68 mm",
        color: "Kırmızı",
      },
    },
    accessories: [
      "Yedek Batarya",
      "Filtre Kitleri",
      "Ekstra Lens",
      "Taşıma Çantası",
      "Tripod",
      "Lens Temizleme Kiti",
    ],
    warranty: "3 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 60,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "2-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["Kapıda Ödeme"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Joshua Blair",
        rating: 5,
        comment: "Father like which base customer itself.",
        date: "2024-03-14",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Manage ready meeting center take.",
        answer: "Never easy follow value team station they.",
        date: "2024-01-21",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    name: "Ürün 2",
    category: "Elektronik",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 2399.66,
    brand: "Marka B",
    stock: 63,
    ratings: {
      average: 3.6,
      count: 380,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "APS-C",
      resolution: "22MP",
      videoResolution: "8K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: true,
        bluetooth: true,
        gps: true,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "Li-ion",
        life: "438 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "452g",
        dimensions: "132 x 90 x 57 mm",
        color: "Kırmızı",
      },
    },
    accessories: ["Ekstra Lens"],
    warranty: "2 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 30,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "3-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["Kredi Kartı", "EFT", "Banka Havalesi", "Kapıda Ödeme"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "William Jones",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "Available break rise.",
        date: "2024-02-28",
      },
      {
        author: "Michael Rodriguez",
        rating: 3,
        comment:
          "Take although possible science suddenly minute responsibility phone.",
        date: "2024-03-25",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Data bit behind fine degree role evidence.",
        answer: "Movement against attention inside sure partner explain.",
        date: "2024-01-22",
      },
      {
        question: "Fill environmental half single quality day whether.",
        answer: "Mind think call policy majority statement authority.",
        date: "2024-03-02",
      },
      {
        question: "No no notice because remain.",
        answer: "System generation source study anyone.",
        date: "2024-03-24",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    name: "Ürün 3",
    category: "Ev & Yaşam",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 3006.21,
    brand: "Marka C",
    stock: 34,
    ratings: {
      average: 4.1,
      count: 137,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Full Frame",
      resolution: "30MP",
      videoResolution: "8K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: false,
        bluetooth: false,
        gps: false,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "Li-ion",
        life: "868 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "728g",
        dimensions: "125 x 67 x 74 mm",
        color: "Kırmızı",
      },
    },
    accessories: [
      "Taşıma Çantası",
      "Tripod",
      "Lens Temizleme Kiti",
      "Ekstra Lens",
    ],
    warranty: "3 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 60,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "5-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["Kripto Para"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "William Reed",
        rating: 5,
        comment: "Executive cultural reality chair.",
        date: "2024-03-08",
      },
      {
        author: "Steven Clark",
        rating: 2,
        comment: "Often kid point article.",
        date: "2024-01-05",
      },
      {
        author: "Nathan Webb",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "Tell person reduce girl.",
        date: "2024-02-26",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Future officer police quite occur possible job.",
        answer: "Appear light capital keep special various economy.",
        date: "2024-01-10",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    name: "Ürün 4",
    category: "Ev & Yaşam",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 3959.69,
    brand: "Marka D",
    stock: 57,
    ratings: {
      average: 3.9,
      count: 177,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Micro Four Thirds",
      resolution: "58MP",
      videoResolution: "1080p",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: true,
        bluetooth: true,
        gps: false,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "Li-ion",
        life: "725 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "589g",
        dimensions: "128 x 101 x 77 mm",
        color: "Kırmızı",
      },
    },
    accessories: ["Taşıma Çantası", "Ekstra Lens"],
    warranty: "3 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 60,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "5-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: [
      "Kapıda Ödeme",
      "Banka Havalesi",
      "Kripto Para",
      "EFT",
      "Kredi Kartı",
    ],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Latoya Wiggins",
        rating: 5,
        comment: "Say avoid other build billion force star pick.",
        date: "2024-02-19",
      },
      {
        author: "Roger Camacho",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Tough ten need nature then.",
        date: "2024-01-22",
      },
      {
        author: "Sandra Brown",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Attention out production white where country.",
        date: "2024-03-20",
      },
      {
        author: "Joy Santiago",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "Per also future.",
        date: "2024-02-15",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "List create young concern.",
        answer: "Prepare school director administration situation gas.",
        date: "2024-03-11",
      },
      {
        question: "Cup account season investment me.",
        answer: "Support election change recent use forward discussion.",
        date: "2024-02-25",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    name: "Ürün 5",
    category: "Elektronik",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 3139.46,
    brand: "Marka E",
    stock: 77,
    ratings: {
      average: 1.9,
      count: 35,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Micro Four Thirds",
      resolution: "33MP",
      videoResolution: "8K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: false,
        bluetooth: true,
        gps: true,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "Li-ion",
        life: "486 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "1025g",
        dimensions: "131 x 115 x 85 mm",
        color: "Siyah",
      },
    },
    accessories: [
      "Ekstra Lens",
      "Lens Temizleme Kiti",
      "Tripod",
      "Taşıma Çantası",
      "Yedek Batarya",
      "Filtre Kitleri",
    ],
    warranty: "3 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 60,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "1-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: [
      "Banka Havalesi",
      "EFT",
      "Kredi Kartı",
      "Kapıda Ödeme",
      "Kripto Para",
    ],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Gabriel Reeves",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "It successful continue adult.",
        date: "2024-02-09",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Body official human program.",
        answer: "Despite line reason administration treatment.",
        date: "2024-03-20",
      },
      {
        question: "Sit others author pressure they.",
        answer: "Now dog until piece painting son receive.",
        date: "2024-02-12",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    name: "Ürün 6",
    category: "Elektronik",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 4435.22,
    brand: "Marka F",
    stock: 3,
    ratings: {
      average: 4.9,
      count: 316,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Full Frame",
      resolution: "58MP",
      videoResolution: "8K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: false,
        bluetooth: false,
        gps: false,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "AA",
        life: "419 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "1492g",
        dimensions: "141 x 82 x 53 mm",
        color: "Gri",
      },
    },
    accessories: ["Yedek Batarya", "Ekstra Lens", "Taşıma Çantası"],
    warranty: "2 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 15,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "3-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["EFT", "Kripto Para", "Banka Havalesi"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Kellie White",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "Save another party wonder.",
        date: "2024-03-16",
      },
      {
        author: "William Wells",
        rating: 5,
        comment: "Campaign race couple four dinner push whether follow.",
        date: "2024-02-07",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Among right so common general knowledge arrive newspaper.",
        answer: "Movie factor miss pressure stay her whom.",
        date: "2024-02-03",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    name: "Ürün 7",
    category: "Ev & Yaşam",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 2887.23,
    brand: "Marka G",
    stock: 60,
    ratings: {
      average: 1.5,
      count: 414,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "APS-C",
      resolution: "50MP",
      videoResolution: "1080p",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: false,
        bluetooth: true,
        gps: true,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "AA",
        life: "937 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "1138g",
        dimensions: "130 x 117 x 39 mm",
        color: "Gri",
      },
    },
    accessories: [
      "Lens Temizleme Kiti",
      "Tripod",
      "Taşıma Çantası",
      "Filtre Kitleri",
    ],
    warranty: "3 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 60,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "3-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: [
      "EFT",
      "Kapıda Ödeme",
      "Banka Havalesi",
      "Kripto Para",
      "Kredi Kartı",
    ],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Robert Richardson",
        rating: 2,
        comment: "Foreign theory as ready age section would including.",
        date: "2024-03-24",
      },
      {
        author: "Jamie Jackson",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Message majority want hotel organization.",
        date: "2024-01-12",
      },
      {
        author: "Maria Castro",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "While truth stuff six turn glass risk production.",
        date: "2024-03-23",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Test majority sometimes throw run reality simply.",
        answer: "Tv case day.",
        date: "2024-02-11",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    name: "Ürün 8",
    category: "Elektronik",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 2409.75,
    brand: "Marka H",
    stock: 1,
    ratings: {
      average: 3.4,
      count: 609,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "APS-C",
      resolution: "14MP",
      videoResolution: "4K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: false,
        bluetooth: true,
        gps: false,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "AA",
        life: "577 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "825g",
        dimensions: "145 x 77 x 56 mm",
        color: "Gri",
      },
    },
    accessories: [
      "Tripod",
      "Lens Temizleme Kiti",
      "Ekstra Lens",
      "Filtre Kitleri",
    ],
    warranty: "2 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 60,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "2-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["Kapıda Ödeme", "Banka Havalesi", "Kredi Kartı"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Michael Hughes",
        rating: 5,
        comment: "Always book system similar.",
        date: "2024-02-03",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Easy career choice cover.",
        answer: "Adult tell political partner market commercial.",
        date: "2024-02-28",
      },
      {
        question: "By hour strategy hospital positive state cover.",
        answer: "Water model likely couple crime right.",
        date: "2024-01-24",
      },
      {
        question: "Still drop strong as.",
        answer: "Pay ahead event movement.",
        date: "2024-02-15",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    name: "Ürün 9",
    category: "Elektronik",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 2022.07,
    brand: "Marka I",
    stock: 86,
    ratings: {
      average: 3.2,
      count: 505,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "APS-C",
      resolution: "26MP",
      videoResolution: "4K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: false,
        bluetooth: true,
        gps: true,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "Li-ion",
        life: "390 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "1223g",
        dimensions: "121 x 103 x 59 mm",
        color: "Kırmızı",
      },
    },
    accessories: ["Lens Temizleme Kiti", "Ekstra Lens", "Yedek Batarya"],
    warranty: "1 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 15,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "3-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: [
      "Kripto Para",
      "Kapıda Ödeme",
      "EFT",
      "Banka Havalesi",
      "Kredi Kartı",
    ],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Shawn Young",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "Attorney thing reflect today.",
        date: "2024-03-23",
      },
      {
        author: "Brian Mueller",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "Everything lot happy tough field.",
        date: "2024-02-24",
      },
      {
        author: "Thomas Cummings",
        rating: 2,
        comment: "Top fire successful weight yourself system.",
        date: "2024-01-07",
      },
      {
        author: "John Grant",
        rating: 5,
        comment: "Act recently beautiful ability six member.",
        date: "2024-02-11",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Agency song car too TV hotel.",
        answer: "Customer senior thank week conference trade age.",
        date: "2024-02-14",
      },
      {
        question: "Run would heart.",
        answer: "Reveal record city seek.",
        date: "2024-03-05",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    name: "Ürün 10",
    category: "Ev & Yaşam",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 329.67,
    brand: "Marka J",
    stock: 95,
    ratings: {
      average: 4.2,
      count: 401,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Micro Four Thirds",
      resolution: "14MP",
      videoResolution: "4K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: true,
        bluetooth: true,
        gps: false,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "Li-ion",
        life: "476 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "877g",
        dimensions: "142 x 113 x 60 mm",
        color: "Siyah",
      },
    },
    accessories: ["Yedek Batarya", "Filtre Kitleri"],
    warranty: "3 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 30,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "7-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["Kredi Kartı", "EFT"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Ricky Walsh",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Home add teacher public career fight consumer.",
        date: "2024-02-03",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "How modern serve receive.",
        answer: "Test hand deep let ok.",
        date: "2024-01-20",
      },
      {
        question: "Will customer half give spring.",
        answer: "Conference interest these prepare citizen data.",
        date: "2024-02-24",
      },
      {
        question: "Education color argue range section.",
        answer: "Form city risk the individual serious.",
        date: "2024-03-22",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    name: "Ürün 11",
    category: "Kişisel Bakım",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 961.31,
    brand: "Marka K",
    stock: 51,
    ratings: {
      average: 2.5,
      count: 357,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "APS-C",
      resolution: "39MP",
      videoResolution: "4K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: false,
        bluetooth: false,
        gps: false,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "AA",
        life: "1000 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "847g",
        dimensions: "131 x 71 x 67 mm",
        color: "Gri",
      },
    },
    accessories: ["Yedek Batarya"],
    warranty: "3 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 15,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "1-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: [
      "EFT",
      "Kredi Kartı",
      "Kapıda Ödeme",
      "Banka Havalesi",
      "Kripto Para",
    ],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Lisa Huber",
        rating: 4,
        comment: "Leave mother could change.",
        date: "2024-01-07",
      },
      {
        author: "Brian Diaz",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Player program try type produce more door.",
        date: "2024-02-12",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Kid example cover impact whose.",
        answer: "Him cut gun building.",
        date: "2024-01-30",
      },
      {
        question: "Laugh democratic section avoid sing.",
        answer: "Allow trip alone response statement.",
        date: "2024-01-10",
      },
      {
        question: "Sometimes wife group government here staff cost.",
        answer: "Different listen career form condition quite whatever.",
        date: "2024-03-17",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    name: "Ürün 12",
    category: "Elektronik",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 427.6,
    brand: "Marka L",
    stock: 55,
    ratings: {
      average: 2.4,
      count: 199,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "APS-C",
      resolution: "55MP",
      videoResolution: "8K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: false,
        bluetooth: true,
        gps: true,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "Li-ion",
        life: "550 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "711g",
        dimensions: "142 x 106 x 89 mm",
        color: "Kırmızı",
      },
    },
    accessories: ["Tripod", "Ekstra Lens", "Lens Temizleme Kiti"],
    warranty: "1 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 60,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "1-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: [
      "Kripto Para",
      "Kredi Kartı",
      "Kapıda Ödeme",
      "EFT",
      "Banka Havalesi",
    ],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Nicholas Padilla",
        rating: 4,
        comment: "View study Republican simple end.",
        date: "2024-02-16",
      },
      {
        author: "Mr. Adam Reeves",
        rating: 5,
        comment: "Kid say book list.",
        date: "2024-02-07",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Full quickly rule camera past.",
        answer: "Behavior recognize better imagine evidence stage.",
        date: "2024-01-05",
      },
      {
        question: "Sometimes issue painting outside.",
        answer: "Somebody some who measure miss.",
        date: "2024-02-01",
      },
      {
        question: "Board bed take hope center according collection office.",
        answer: "Economy blue carry education military employee.",
        date: "2024-02-13",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    name: "Ürün 13",
    category: "Elektronik",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 3972.09,
    brand: "Marka M",
    stock: 54,
    ratings: {
      average: 4.0,
      count: 444,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Full Frame",
      resolution: "46MP",
      videoResolution: "1080p",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: true,
        bluetooth: true,
        gps: false,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "Li-ion",
        life: "827 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "488g",
        dimensions: "130 x 77 x 41 mm",
        color: "Gri",
      },
    },
    accessories: ["Filtre Kitleri"],
    warranty: "3 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 60,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "3-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["Kapıda Ödeme", "EFT"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "John Smith",
        rating: 2,
        comment: "Suggest politics ground instead power great watch.",
        date: "2024-01-05",
      },
      {
        author: "Lawrence Obrien",
        rating: 2,
        comment: "Significant own question trade tree exactly.",
        date: "2024-02-09",
      },
      {
        author: "David Ochoa",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Law loss example bring heavy people.",
        date: "2024-02-27",
      },
      {
        author: "Kristin Hines",
        rating: 2,
        comment: "Camera professor write leg.",
        date: "2024-01-07",
      },
      {
        author: "Brian Vaughan",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "Although industry expect hear end.",
        date: "2024-01-12",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Remain own economic want.",
        answer: "Pattern someone fall look let cold particular.",
        date: "2024-03-05",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    name: "Ürün 14",
    category: "Ev & Yaşam",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 793.26,
    brand: "Marka N",
    stock: 53,
    ratings: {
      average: 2.6,
      count: 734,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Full Frame",
      resolution: "49MP",
      videoResolution: "4K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: false,
        bluetooth: false,
        gps: false,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "AA",
        life: "498 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "1242g",
        dimensions: "112 x 68 x 100 mm",
        color: "Gri",
      },
    },
    accessories: [
      "Yedek Batarya",
      "Tripod",
      "Ekstra Lens",
      "Lens Temizleme Kiti",
      "Filtre Kitleri",
      "Taşıma Çantası",
    ],
    warranty: "1 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 60,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "1-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: [
      "Kripto Para",
      "Kredi Kartı",
      "Banka Havalesi",
      "EFT",
      "Kapıda Ödeme",
    ],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Christopher Harris",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Give role turn player close.",
        date: "2024-02-28",
      },
      {
        author: "Dustin Lee",
        rating: 5,
        comment: "Plant suddenly plan thank.",
        date: "2024-03-11",
      },
      {
        author: "Raymond Brooks",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Some conference agreement.",
        date: "2024-02-22",
      },
      {
        author: "Michele Mcmillan",
        rating: 4,
        comment: "Similar material live add cover bring.",
        date: "2024-02-20",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Blood tax however reflect.",
        answer: "Mention range will morning.",
        date: "2024-03-13",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    name: "Ürün 15",
    category: "Kişisel Bakım",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 4439.9,
    brand: "Marka O",
    stock: 99,
    ratings: {
      average: 2.0,
      count: 101,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Micro Four Thirds",
      resolution: "32MP",
      videoResolution: "1080p",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: false,
        bluetooth: false,
        gps: false,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "AA",
        life: "467 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "1075g",
        dimensions: "144 x 117 x 98 mm",
        color: "Siyah",
      },
    },
    accessories: ["Lens Temizleme Kiti"],
    warranty: "2 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 15,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "3-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["Kapıda Ödeme", "Kredi Kartı", "Kripto Para", "EFT"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Tracy Dyer",
        rating: 5,
        comment: "Team main no different our smile interview.",
        date: "2024-01-31",
      },
      {
        author: "John Crawford",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "Likely into figure hot world mother.",
        date: "2024-03-10",
      },
      {
        author: "Mrs. Hannah Freeman",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "Good share the capital painting thus.",
        date: "2024-01-17",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "City blood his short owner part.",
        answer: "Between TV natural language drug Congress everybody.",
        date: "2024-01-05",
      },
      {
        question: "Support kind democratic too.",
        answer: "I tax player mission pay say west high.",
        date: "2024-02-27",
      },
      {
        question: "Rise agency quality song billion.",
        answer: "High apply table course evening.",
        date: "2024-03-17",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 16,
    name: "Ürün 16",
    category: "Elektronik",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 3355.07,
    brand: "Marka P",
    stock: 88,
    ratings: {
      average: 2.9,
      count: 358,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Full Frame",
      resolution: "27MP",
      videoResolution: "1080p",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: true,
        bluetooth: false,
        gps: true,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "Li-ion",
        life: "713 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "998g",
        dimensions: "100 x 122 x 45 mm",
        color: "Siyah",
      },
    },
    accessories: ["Lens Temizleme Kiti", "Tripod"],
    warranty: "3 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 30,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "1-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["Banka Havalesi"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Matthew Russo",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "Partner lawyer whom political writer statement it.",
        date: "2024-01-01",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Magazine recently model.",
        answer: "Purpose somebody media similar feeling six.",
        date: "2024-01-23",
      },
      {
        question: "Everybody become must agree.",
        answer: "Thus teach this in well.",
        date: "2024-01-11",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 17,
    name: "Ürün 17",
    category: "Ev & Yaşam",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 3898.33,
    brand: "Marka Q",
    stock: 6,
    ratings: {
      average: 4.4,
      count: 289,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Full Frame",
      resolution: "39MP",
      videoResolution: "8K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: false,
        bluetooth: false,
        gps: true,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "AA",
        life: "610 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "1368g",
        dimensions: "133 x 84 x 89 mm",
        color: "Gri",
      },
    },
    accessories: ["Taşıma Çantası", "Ekstra Lens", "Tripod", "Filtre Kitleri"],
    warranty: "2 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 30,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "1-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["EFT", "Kapıda Ödeme"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Patricia Burns",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "Consider remain woman trial perhaps health long.",
        date: "2024-03-06",
      },
      {
        author: "Donna Garcia",
        rating: 5,
        comment: "Argue gas research spring group push near.",
        date: "2024-01-17",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Mention machine suddenly.",
        answer: "Debate wait democratic item enter.",
        date: "2024-02-29",
      },
      {
        question: "Fly inside fight author final different return understand.",
        answer: "Out information listen control.",
        date: "2024-01-31",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 18,
    name: "Ürün 18",
    category: "Ev & Yaşam",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 669.81,
    brand: "Marka R",
    stock: 15,
    ratings: {
      average: 4.5,
      count: 57,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Micro Four Thirds",
      resolution: "31MP",
      videoResolution: "4K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: false,
        bluetooth: false,
        gps: false,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "Li-ion",
        life: "426 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "1174g",
        dimensions: "145 x 121 x 100 mm",
        color: "Siyah",
      },
    },
    accessories: ["Ekstra Lens", "Filtre Kitleri", "Tripod", "Yedek Batarya"],
    warranty: "2 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 15,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "1-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: [
      "EFT",
      "Kripto Para",
      "Banka Havalesi",
      "Kredi Kartı",
      "Kapıda Ödeme",
    ],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Paul Daugherty",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Eat field economy or long measure newspaper ago.",
        date: "2024-02-22",
      },
      {
        author: "Ashley Russell",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Father long edge whole cut tend.",
        date: "2024-03-08",
      },
      {
        author: "Gabriel Banks",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Shake blood central.",
        date: "2024-01-09",
      },
      {
        author: "Scott Lopez",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "Degree knowledge avoid which.",
        date: "2024-02-08",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Report situation player central middle number.",
        answer: "Family put nothing agent onto young front.",
        date: "2024-01-27",
      },
      {
        question: "Local exist coach since serve.",
        answer: "Think indeed investment along during sign chance.",
        date: "2024-01-29",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 19,
    name: "Ürün 19",
    category: "Elektronik",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 566.14,
    brand: "Marka S",
    stock: 44,
    ratings: {
      average: 1.7,
      count: 887,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Micro Four Thirds",
      resolution: "28MP",
      videoResolution: "8K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: true,
        bluetooth: true,
        gps: false,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "Li-ion",
        life: "991 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "766g",
        dimensions: "100 x 72 x 35 mm",
        color: "Mavi",
      },
    },
    accessories: ["Lens Temizleme Kiti", "Yedek Batarya"],
    warranty: "1 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 15,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "1-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: [
      "Kapıda Ödeme",
      "Kripto Para",
      "Banka Havalesi",
      "Kredi Kartı",
    ],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Peter Hale",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Health sing green dinner must important.",
        date: "2024-01-09",
      },
      {
        author: "Laura Hall",
        rating: 4,
        comment: "Type quality poor me herself.",
        date: "2024-03-23",
      },
      {
        author: "Mckenzie Fowler",
        rating: 2,
        comment: "Budget away and southern if usually yet hotel.",
        date: "2024-02-17",
      },
      {
        author: "John Henry",
        rating: 5,
        comment: "Miss dog establish.",
        date: "2024-01-23",
      },
      {
        author: "Kevin Reyes",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Employee image science plant how.",
        date: "2024-01-29",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "East partner college about laugh sport.",
        answer: "Do less which officer.",
        date: "2024-01-03",
      },
      {
        question: "Around street clearly market beyond open think.",
        answer: "Country place three.",
        date: "2024-02-07",
      },
      {
        question: "Receive write teach answer a husband.",
        answer: "Manage art lay product fill.",
        date: "2024-01-11",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 20,
    name: "Ürün 20",
    category: "Ev & Yaşam",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 4509.33,
    brand: "Marka T",
    stock: 25,
    ratings: {
      average: 1.9,
      count: 99,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "APS-C",
      resolution: "40MP",
      videoResolution: "8K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: false,
        bluetooth: true,
        gps: true,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "Li-ion",
        life: "890 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "1121g",
        dimensions: "148 x 61 x 97 mm",
        color: "Mavi",
      },
    },
    accessories: [
      "Lens Temizleme Kiti",
      "Filtre Kitleri",
      "Yedek Batarya",
      "Tripod",
      "Ekstra Lens",
    ],
    warranty: "2 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 15,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "1-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: [
      "Banka Havalesi",
      "Kripto Para",
      "EFT",
      "Kredi Kartı",
      "Kapıda Ödeme",
    ],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Christine Shaw",
        rating: 2,
        comment: "Write try policy good.",
        date: "2024-03-12",
      },
      {
        author: "Michael Freeman",
        rating: 2,
        comment: "Say it western sit.",
        date: "2024-01-28",
      },
      {
        author: "Samantha Kelly",
        rating: 4,
        comment: "Day despite really some film ago.",
        date: "2024-03-04",
      },
      {
        author: "Kevin Shaw",
        rating: 5,
        comment: "Bed work financial letter raise.",
        date: "2024-02-23",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Guess television if.",
        answer: "Size relate government speech west paper read.",
        date: "2024-03-09",
      },
      {
        question: "Around stand a surface agreement commercial give even.",
        answer: "Against indicate remember.",
        date: "2024-01-27",
      },
      {
        question: "Model economic turn campaign large response.",
        answer: "Allow might first occur south management left.",
        date: "2024-03-19",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 21,
    name: "Ürün 21",
    category: "Elektronik",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 2634.75,
    brand: "Marka U",
    stock: 85,
    ratings: {
      average: 3.7,
      count: 75,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Full Frame",
      resolution: "13MP",
      videoResolution: "4K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: false,
        bluetooth: false,
        gps: true,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "Li-ion",
        life: "528 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "1034g",
        dimensions: "120 x 124 x 74 mm",
        color: "Kırmızı",
      },
    },
    accessories: ["Taşıma Çantası", "Ekstra Lens"],
    warranty: "1 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 60,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "2-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["Kredi Kartı", "EFT"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "George Bowers",
        rating: 4,
        comment: "Plant interest floor land way energy.",
        date: "2024-02-22",
      },
      {
        author: "Andrew Snyder",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Wrong fire again move put in nor mean.",
        date: "2024-01-14",
      },
      {
        author: "Thomas Nguyen",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Rate upon without in.",
        date: "2024-03-18",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Wife air look assume show professional visit deal.",
        answer: "Three ball usually teacher believe author.",
        date: "2024-01-17",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Deal everybody strong evidence wide everything summer statement.",
        answer: "Book girl however.",
        date: "2024-01-19",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 22,
    name: "Ürün 22",
    category: "Kişisel Bakım",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 1547.25,
    brand: "Marka V",
    stock: 72,
    ratings: {
      average: 2.8,
      count: 131,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Micro Four Thirds",
      resolution: "38MP",
      videoResolution: "1080p",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: true,
        bluetooth: true,
        gps: true,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "Li-ion",
        life: "570 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "1109g",
        dimensions: "117 x 78 x 63 mm",
        color: "Siyah",
      },
    },
    accessories: [
      "Ekstra Lens",
      "Lens Temizleme Kiti",
      "Taşıma Çantası",
      "Filtre Kitleri",
    ],
    warranty: "2 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 15,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "5-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["Kripto Para", "EFT", "Kredi Kartı", "Kapıda Ödeme"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Andrew Moore",
        rating: 2,
        comment: "Pick leader build green across feel.",
        date: "2024-02-28",
      },
      {
        author: "Sean Richard",
        rating: 5,
        comment: "Happen probably lose they stock personal above.",
        date: "2024-01-16",
      },
      {
        author: "Ethan Baker",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "How direction establish staff article receive.",
        date: "2024-02-17",
      },
      {
        author: "Melissa Watts",
        rating: 4,
        comment: "Standard lay blue statement foreign.",
        date: "2024-02-25",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "View vote senior ground girl his stop.",
        answer: "Member model threat stop history feel.",
        date: "2024-02-10",
      },
      {
        question: "Assume everyone hot peace.",
        answer: "Nearly reach religious husband.",
        date: "2024-03-24",
      },
      {
        question: "Administration anyone I question recently level up.",
        answer: "Language research cover vote pretty sense state participant.",
        date: "2024-03-07",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 23,
    name: "Ürün 23",
    category: "Elektronik",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 1897.86,
    brand: "Marka W",
    stock: 12,
    ratings: {
      average: 1.7,
      count: 479,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "APS-C",
      resolution: "46MP",
      videoResolution: "1080p",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: true,
        bluetooth: false,
        gps: false,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "Li-ion",
        life: "376 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "1053g",
        dimensions: "121 x 94 x 66 mm",
        color: "Siyah",
      },
    },
    accessories: [
      "Tripod",
      "Yedek Batarya",
      "Lens Temizleme Kiti",
      "Taşıma Çantası",
      "Filtre Kitleri",
      "Ekstra Lens",
    ],
    warranty: "2 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 15,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "3-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["Kapıda Ödeme", "Banka Havalesi"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Alyssa Yu",
        rating: 2,
        comment: "Employee structure manager report away.",
        date: "2024-01-26",
      },
      {
        author: "Jonathan Holden",
        rating: 2,
        comment: "Participant woman since yard course.",
        date: "2024-03-06",
      },
      {
        author: "Denise Anderson",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Attention crime share arrive anything cell smile grow.",
        date: "2024-02-20",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Green soldier music some professional respond.",
        answer: "Call mission hear tax open world.",
        date: "2024-02-24",
      },
      {
        question: "Could beautiful go likely throw.",
        answer: "I reach imagine item indeed reduce great last.",
        date: "2024-01-12",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 24,
    name: "Ürün 24",
    category: "Ev & Yaşam",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 197.4,
    brand: "Marka X",
    stock: 18,
    ratings: {
      average: 3.0,
      count: 937,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "APS-C",
      resolution: "53MP",
      videoResolution: "8K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: true,
        bluetooth: false,
        gps: true,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "Li-ion",
        life: "558 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "450g",
        dimensions: "130 x 96 x 65 mm",
        color: "Kırmızı",
      },
    },
    accessories: ["Lens Temizleme Kiti"],
    warranty: "2 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 60,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "5-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["Kapıda Ödeme", "Kripto Para"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Pam Herring",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "By husband then campaign trip war.",
        date: "2024-03-18",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Event budget American nearly put.",
        answer: "Investment family choice best.",
        date: "2024-03-05",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 25,
    name: "Ürün 25",
    category: "Elektronik",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 1482.3,
    brand: "Marka Y",
    stock: 47,
    ratings: {
      average: 3.6,
      count: 514,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Full Frame",
      resolution: "55MP",
      videoResolution: "4K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: true,
        bluetooth: true,
        gps: true,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "Li-ion",
        life: "423 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "686g",
        dimensions: "122 x 70 x 55 mm",
        color: "Gri",
      },
    },
    accessories: ["Tripod", "Lens Temizleme Kiti"],
    warranty: "1 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 15,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "5-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: [
      "Kredi Kartı",
      "Kapıda Ödeme",
      "Kripto Para",
      "EFT",
      "Banka Havalesi",
    ],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Teresa Pena",
        rating: 4,
        comment: "Continue law store should.",
        date: "2024-03-24",
      },
      {
        author: "Maria Norris",
        rating: 4,
        comment: "Former about outside use take.",
        date: "2024-02-02",
      },
      {
        author: "Paul White",
        rating: 2,
        comment: "Program other speech lot simple PM generation for.",
        date: "2024-01-15",
      },
      {
        author: "James Chung",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Administration determine project culture water talk seem.",
        date: "2024-01-29",
      },
      {
        author: "Tracy Lewis",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "Key behind new degree reflect attorney.",
        date: "2024-01-11",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Very break charge hot soldier.",
        answer: "Peace more keep.",
        date: "2024-01-19",
      },
      {
        question: "Also letter organization wall modern game trade.",
        answer: "Reflect lot find hold.",
        date: "2024-02-09",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 26,
    name: "Ürün 26",
    category: "Ev & Yaşam",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 4440.04,
    brand: "Marka Z",
    stock: 5,
    ratings: {
      average: 2.0,
      count: 392,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Full Frame",
      resolution: "45MP",
      videoResolution: "1080p",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: true,
        bluetooth: true,
        gps: true,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "Li-ion",
        life: "706 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "1326g",
        dimensions: "133 x 108 x 50 mm",
        color: "Mavi",
      },
    },
    accessories: [
      "Yedek Batarya",
      "Lens Temizleme Kiti",
      "Ekstra Lens",
      "Taşıma Çantası",
      "Filtre Kitleri",
      "Tripod",
    ],
    warranty: "2 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 60,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "1-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["Kredi Kartı", "Kapıda Ödeme", "EFT"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Joseph Thompson",
        rating: 2,
        comment: "Nature mother thank offer man control.",
        date: "2024-01-02",
      },
      {
        author: "Alexandra Fuller",
        rating: 2,
        comment: "Hundred mean often discover design action.",
        date: "2024-03-16",
      },
      {
        author: "Donna Johnson",
        rating: 4,
        comment: "Kid investment goal medical break seek.",
        date: "2024-02-24",
      },
      {
        author: "Leah Caldwell",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "Clearly save series keep.",
        date: "2024-02-09",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Ok key down wind.",
        answer: "Build serve lose together.",
        date: "2024-02-02",
      },
      {
        question: "Environmental would certainly front what good.",
        answer: "Read enough rock physical region nor although.",
        date: "2024-02-09",
      },
      {
        question: "Family fund surface fine long step.",
        answer: "Relate later hold perhaps these follow position nature.",
        date: "2024-02-06",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 27,
    name: "Ürün 27",
    category: "Elektronik",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 1094.36,
    brand: "Marka [",
    stock: 26,
    ratings: {
      average: 2.0,
      count: 157,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Micro Four Thirds",
      resolution: "16MP",
      videoResolution: "1080p",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: true,
        bluetooth: false,
        gps: true,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "Li-ion",
        life: "748 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "416g",
        dimensions: "142 x 81 x 73 mm",
        color: "Gri",
      },
    },
    accessories: [
      "Taşıma Çantası",
      "Lens Temizleme Kiti",
      "Tripod",
      "Ekstra Lens",
      "Filtre Kitleri",
      "Yedek Batarya",
    ],
    warranty: "2 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 60,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "2-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: [
      "Kredi Kartı",
      "Banka Havalesi",
      "Kapıda Ödeme",
      "Kripto Para",
    ],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Martin Moore",
        rating: 5,
        comment: "Yourself artist debate six clearly.",
        date: "2024-02-01",
      },
      {
        author: "Pamela Solis",
        rating: 2,
        comment: "Wind not employee explain know perhaps daughter.",
        date: "2024-01-27",
      },
      {
        author: "Jennifer Francis",
        rating: 4,
        comment: "Mission serious send.",
        date: "2024-03-06",
      },
      {
        author: "Nicole Duarte",
        rating: 5,
        comment: "Address help similar purpose middle cause.",
        date: "2024-01-12",
      },
      {
        author: "Jeremy Hernandez",
        rating: 5,
        comment: "Card black kitchen last significant cultural as.",
        date: "2024-01-30",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Real attention section enough summer.",
        answer: "Baby lot day mission.",
        date: "2024-03-04",
      },
      {
        question: "Understand early group present structure base trade.",
        answer: "Industry particularly serve product.",
        date: "2024-01-18",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 28,
    name: "Ürün 28",
    category: "Elektronik",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 1027.36,
    brand: "Marka \\",
    stock: 93,
    ratings: {
      average: 4.2,
      count: 943,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "APS-C",
      resolution: "52MP",
      videoResolution: "4K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: true,
        bluetooth: true,
        gps: false,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "Li-ion",
        life: "533 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "908g",
        dimensions: "110 x 70 x 66 mm",
        color: "Gri",
      },
    },
    accessories: [
      "Taşıma Çantası",
      "Lens Temizleme Kiti",
      "Ekstra Lens",
      "Tripod",
    ],
    warranty: "2 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 15,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "3-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["Banka Havalesi", "EFT", "Kredi Kartı", "Kripto Para"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Dawn Jackson",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Plan book not capital whether itself.",
        date: "2024-01-20",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Particular care sign manage seven provide capital into.",
        answer: "The on unit coach wrong catch.",
        date: "2024-01-08",
      },
      {
        question: "Stock ever itself food poor surface over.",
        answer: "Rule wonder someone stage.",
        date: "2024-02-21",
      },
      {
        question: "Which miss lead.",
        answer: "Really party finally important receive.",
        date: "2024-01-11",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 29,
    name: "Ürün 29",
    category: "Elektronik",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 3002.71,
    brand: "Marka ]",
    stock: 26,
    ratings: {
      average: 1.9,
      count: 716,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Full Frame",
      resolution: "23MP",
      videoResolution: "4K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: false,
        bluetooth: false,
        gps: true,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "AA",
        life: "324 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "581g",
        dimensions: "150 x 76 x 99 mm",
        color: "Kırmızı",
      },
    },
    accessories: ["Taşıma Çantası", "Filtre Kitleri"],
    warranty: "1 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 30,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "7-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: [
      "EFT",
      "Banka Havalesi",
      "Kapıda Ödeme",
      "Kredi Kartı",
      "Kripto Para",
    ],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Chloe Aguilar",
        rating: 2,
        comment:
          "Already similar hear professor recently official throughout civil.",
        date: "2024-02-25",
      },
      {
        author: "Charles Beltran",
        rating: 5,
        comment: "Medical free century approach.",
        date: "2024-01-09",
      },
      {
        author: "Jimmy Fisher",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "Outside product real next enough certain white.",
        date: "2024-01-04",
      },
      {
        author: "Margaret Potter",
        rating: 4,
        comment: "Course town consumer sport on.",
        date: "2024-03-09",
      },
      {
        author: "Christopher Harris",
        rating: 2,
        comment: "Those board throw whose production hope two develop.",
        date: "2024-02-17",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Region other join five eye few.",
        answer: "Letter give sea radio develop not.",
        date: "2024-03-08",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 30,
    name: "Ürün 30",
    category: "Elektronik",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 842.81,
    brand: "Marka ^",
    stock: 7,
    ratings: {
      average: 3.6,
      count: 762,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Full Frame",
      resolution: "33MP",
      videoResolution: "1080p",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: true,
        bluetooth: false,
        gps: false,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "AA",
        life: "990 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "722g",
        dimensions: "142 x 84 x 34 mm",
        color: "Kırmızı",
      },
    },
    accessories: [
      "Taşıma Çantası",
      "Filtre Kitleri",
      "Yedek Batarya",
      "Ekstra Lens",
      "Lens Temizleme Kiti",
    ],
    warranty: "3 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 30,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "2-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["Kripto Para", "Kapıda Ödeme"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "William Gomez",
        rating: 5,
        comment: "Establish market easy writer goal wind.",
        date: "2024-03-11",
      },
      {
        author: "Mrs. Megan Gibson DVM",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Tough while indicate dark data some go.",
        date: "2024-03-15",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Realize financial anything.",
        answer: "President degree animal glass teach race.",
        date: "2024-03-18",
      },
      {
        question: "Suffer two business former land.",
        answer: "Skin peace performance.",
        date: "2024-02-29",
      },
      {
        question: "Republican cold would certainly big stay.",
        answer: "Thus listen attack stuff.",
        date: "2024-01-14",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 31,
    name: "Ürün 31",
    category: "Kişisel Bakım",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 1348.88,
    brand: "Marka _",
    stock: 29,
    ratings: {
      average: 3.4,
      count: 749,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Full Frame",
      resolution: "20MP",
      videoResolution: "8K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: true,
        bluetooth: false,
        gps: true,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "AA",
        life: "746 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "1357g",
        dimensions: "120 x 120 x 96 mm",
        color: "Siyah",
      },
    },
    accessories: ["Lens Temizleme Kiti", "Filtre Kitleri"],
    warranty: "2 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 60,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "2-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["EFT", "Banka Havalesi"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Louis Wright",
        rating: 4,
        comment: "Week must sense executive agent city rather.",
        date: "2024-03-25",
      },
      {
        author: "Heidi Garcia",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Social pressure even successful mouth.",
        date: "2024-02-23",
      },
      {
        author: "Johnny Sims",
        rating: 4,
        comment: "Meet really answer three add.",
        date: "2024-01-12",
      },
      {
        author: "Tina Brown",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "Green outside toward dream condition such.",
        date: "2024-03-24",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Send television foreign thank read wonder.",
        answer: "Protect population miss likely.",
        date: "2024-02-11",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 32,
    name: "Ürün 32",
    category: "Ev & Yaşam",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 4415.77,
    brand: "Marka `",
    stock: 29,
    ratings: {
      average: 4.1,
      count: 39,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "APS-C",
      resolution: "23MP",
      videoResolution: "1080p",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: false,
        bluetooth: true,
        gps: true,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "AA",
        life: "789 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "1259g",
        dimensions: "142 x 123 x 41 mm",
        color: "Gri",
      },
    },
    accessories: [
      "Lens Temizleme Kiti",
      "Ekstra Lens",
      "Filtre Kitleri",
      "Yedek Batarya",
      "Taşıma Çantası",
      "Tripod",
    ],
    warranty: "3 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 60,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "5-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: [
      "Kapıda Ödeme",
      "Kripto Para",
      "EFT",
      "Banka Havalesi",
      "Kredi Kartı",
    ],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Kathryn Shah",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "Sometimes beat real who chair soldier amount garden.",
        date: "2024-02-20",
      },
      {
        author: "Amanda Taylor",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "Too organization speak put always.",
        date: "2024-01-24",
      },
      {
        author: "Dana Martin",
        rating: 5,
        comment: "Organization because professor threat art tree.",
        date: "2024-01-15",
      },
      {
        author: "Derek Beck",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "Interview agent town.",
        date: "2024-02-07",
      },
      {
        author: "Eric Brooks DVM",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "Structure certainly expert attack.",
        date: "2024-02-10",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Political house join fill much lawyer next.",
        answer: "Friend team home control sign.",
        date: "2024-03-19",
      },
      {
        question: "School show prevent member page.",
        answer: "Second need member Mr tend history usually TV.",
        date: "2024-03-11",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 33,
    name: "Ürün 33",
    category: "Ev & Yaşam",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 2335.05,
    brand: "Marka a",
    stock: 12,
    ratings: {
      average: 4.2,
      count: 884,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "APS-C",
      resolution: "13MP",
      videoResolution: "1080p",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: false,
        bluetooth: false,
        gps: false,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "AA",
        life: "919 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "1045g",
        dimensions: "122 x 84 x 38 mm",
        color: "Kırmızı",
      },
    },
    accessories: [
      "Tripod",
      "Ekstra Lens",
      "Taşıma Çantası",
      "Filtre Kitleri",
      "Lens Temizleme Kiti",
      "Yedek Batarya",
    ],
    warranty: "3 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 30,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "3-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["Kapıda Ödeme"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Cassandra Anderson",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "Matter TV husband wrong family as.",
        date: "2024-03-15",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Age see yeah medical we force.",
        answer: "Technology conference toward drop.",
        date: "2024-02-06",
      },
      {
        question: "Yeah four protect performance.",
        answer: "Base eye peace analysis season good option stand.",
        date: "2024-01-20",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 34,
    name: "Ürün 34",
    category: "Elektronik",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 1927.43,
    brand: "Marka b",
    stock: 2,
    ratings: {
      average: 1.0,
      count: 50,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "APS-C",
      resolution: "27MP",
      videoResolution: "1080p",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: true,
        bluetooth: false,
        gps: true,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "AA",
        life: "941 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "507g",
        dimensions: "116 x 102 x 64 mm",
        color: "Mavi",
      },
    },
    accessories: [
      "Filtre Kitleri",
      "Taşıma Çantası",
      "Lens Temizleme Kiti",
      "Ekstra Lens",
      "Yedek Batarya",
      "Tripod",
    ],
    warranty: "1 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 30,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "1-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["EFT", "Kredi Kartı"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Sarah Silva",
        rating: 2,
        comment: "Figure similar each space.",
        date: "2024-01-20",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Pay occur each world protect.",
        answer: "Stuff song many field smile.",
        date: "2024-03-07",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 35,
    name: "Ürün 35",
    category: "Ev & Yaşam",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 2495.24,
    brand: "Marka c",
    stock: 61,
    ratings: {
      average: 4.7,
      count: 213,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Micro Four Thirds",
      resolution: "14MP",
      videoResolution: "4K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: false,
        bluetooth: true,
        gps: false,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "AA",
        life: "603 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "577g",
        dimensions: "126 x 115 x 99 mm",
        color: "Mavi",
      },
    },
    accessories: [
      "Taşıma Çantası",
      "Tripod",
      "Filtre Kitleri",
      "Yedek Batarya",
    ],
    warranty: "3 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 30,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "5-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["Kredi Kartı", "Banka Havalesi", "Kapıda Ödeme"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Brian Schmidt",
        rating: 4,
        comment: "Store good particular smile blue describe.",
        date: "2024-01-15",
      },
      {
        author: "Michael Taylor",
        rating: 5,
        comment: "Everything property senior who table others.",
        date: "2024-02-06",
      },
      {
        author: "Lindsey Thomas",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "View three everyone explain staff as.",
        date: "2024-01-30",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Yet majority look you throughout.",
        answer: "Such his leader area senior.",
        date: "2024-02-21",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 36,
    name: "Ürün 36",
    category: "Kişisel Bakım",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 2008.68,
    brand: "Marka d",
    stock: 13,
    ratings: {
      average: 1.5,
      count: 184,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "APS-C",
      resolution: "49MP",
      videoResolution: "1080p",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: true,
        bluetooth: true,
        gps: true,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "AA",
        life: "464 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "1034g",
        dimensions: "139 x 111 x 49 mm",
        color: "Mavi",
      },
    },
    accessories: [
      "Filtre Kitleri",
      "Lens Temizleme Kiti",
      "Tripod",
      "Taşıma Çantası",
      "Yedek Batarya",
      "Ekstra Lens",
    ],
    warranty: "1 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 30,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "5-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: [
      "EFT",
      "Kapıda Ödeme",
      "Kredi Kartı",
      "Kripto Para",
      "Banka Havalesi",
    ],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Christopher Mullins",
        rating: 5,
        comment: "Unit girl society group.",
        date: "2024-03-18",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Movie want factor attention different trial avoid cover.",
        answer: "Into woman usually do size.",
        date: "2024-01-15",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 37,
    name: "Ürün 37",
    category: "Kişisel Bakım",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 3891.62,
    brand: "Marka e",
    stock: 52,
    ratings: {
      average: 3.2,
      count: 868,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "APS-C",
      resolution: "32MP",
      videoResolution: "4K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: true,
        bluetooth: true,
        gps: true,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "Li-ion",
        life: "354 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "1326g",
        dimensions: "133 x 125 x 31 mm",
        color: "Mavi",
      },
    },
    accessories: ["Taşıma Çantası", "Lens Temizleme Kiti", "Ekstra Lens"],
    warranty: "3 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 60,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "3-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["Kapıda Ödeme"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Ricardo Ferrell",
        rating: 5,
        comment: "Piece fall cover best role.",
        date: "2024-02-27",
      },
      {
        author: "Dr. Kristina Hopkins DDS",
        rating: 2,
        comment: "Tell under turn us choice three town.",
        date: "2024-03-22",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Type floor boy television worry explain he.",
        answer: "Must major role parent ground night worry.",
        date: "2024-01-18",
      },
      {
        question: "Series loss learn.",
        answer: "Increase manager religious ahead support who edge.",
        date: "2024-03-14",
      },
      {
        question: "Result executive painting.",
        answer: "Keep fear turn fish ask alone.",
        date: "2024-03-06",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 38,
    name: "Ürün 38",
    category: "Elektronik",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 4156.47,
    brand: "Marka f",
    stock: 86,
    ratings: {
      average: 4.1,
      count: 745,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Micro Four Thirds",
      resolution: "21MP",
      videoResolution: "1080p",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: true,
        bluetooth: true,
        gps: false,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "AA",
        life: "470 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "1179g",
        dimensions: "120 x 124 x 32 mm",
        color: "Siyah",
      },
    },
    accessories: [
      "Ekstra Lens",
      "Lens Temizleme Kiti",
      "Tripod",
      "Yedek Batarya",
      "Filtre Kitleri",
      "Taşıma Çantası",
    ],
    warranty: "1 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 30,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "3-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: [
      "Kredi Kartı",
      "Kapıda Ödeme",
      "Banka Havalesi",
      "Kripto Para",
      "EFT",
    ],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Leah Young",
        rating: 4,
        comment: "Defense rule manage too black fear carry.",
        date: "2024-03-11",
      },
      {
        author: "Michael Gaines",
        rating: 2,
        comment: "Blue practice scientist or.",
        date: "2024-02-03",
      },
      {
        author: "John Davis",
        rating: 5,
        comment: "Challenge computer into sell able.",
        date: "2024-01-18",
      },
      {
        author: "Krista Smith",
        rating: 4,
        comment: "Enter blood behavior animal box.",
        date: "2024-02-14",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Significant base join middle should couple unit popular.",
        answer: "Whether represent here their ask.",
        date: "2024-02-24",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 39,
    name: "Ürün 39",
    category: "Kişisel Bakım",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 4771.07,
    brand: "Marka g",
    stock: 0,
    ratings: {
      average: 1.8,
      count: 62,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Full Frame",
      resolution: "25MP",
      videoResolution: "1080p",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: true,
        bluetooth: true,
        gps: true,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "AA",
        life: "786 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "741g",
        dimensions: "105 x 100 x 95 mm",
        color: "Gri",
      },
    },
    accessories: [
      "Yedek Batarya",
      "Ekstra Lens",
      "Taşıma Çantası",
      "Tripod",
      "Lens Temizleme Kiti",
    ],
    warranty: "1 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 15,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "1-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["EFT", "Kapıda Ödeme"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Laura Andrews",
        rating: 4,
        comment: "Parent writer human sell economy bring.",
        date: "2024-03-10",
      },
      {
        author: "Laura Hall",
        rating: 5,
        comment: "Either cause assume wife.",
        date: "2024-02-27",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Congress little American nature.",
        answer: "Sound firm place owner scientist.",
        date: "2024-03-19",
      },
      {
        question: "That free themselves simply agree physical fine majority.",
        answer: "Score able science order where.",
        date: "2024-01-25",
      },
      {
        question: "Fill specific large baby.",
        answer: "Girl catch study many.",
        date: "2024-01-17",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 40,
    name: "Ürün 40",
    category: "Kişisel Bakım",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 1162.31,
    brand: "Marka h",
    stock: 4,
    ratings: {
      average: 3.1,
      count: 167,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Micro Four Thirds",
      resolution: "58MP",
      videoResolution: "4K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: true,
        bluetooth: true,
        gps: true,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "Li-ion",
        life: "495 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "971g",
        dimensions: "137 x 65 x 46 mm",
        color: "Siyah",
      },
    },
    accessories: [
      "Yedek Batarya",
      "Tripod",
      "Lens Temizleme Kiti",
      "Ekstra Lens",
      "Taşıma Çantası",
    ],
    warranty: "2 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 60,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "1-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["EFT", "Kapıda Ödeme", "Banka Havalesi", "Kredi Kartı"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Gabriella Lee",
        rating: 5,
        comment: "Short experience hundred reality themselves money relate.",
        date: "2024-03-04",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Able product after instead although five involve.",
        answer: "Suffer fear away lot then magazine less.",
        date: "2024-02-03",
      },
      {
        question: "Develop away share control because enter.",
        answer: "Tend more wide response music possible.",
        date: "2024-01-16",
      },
      {
        question: "More item feeling everybody.",
        answer: "Control system leader occur.",
        date: "2024-02-20",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 41,
    name: "Ürün 41",
    category: "Elektronik",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 591.38,
    brand: "Marka i",
    stock: 71,
    ratings: {
      average: 1.1,
      count: 275,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Full Frame",
      resolution: "56MP",
      videoResolution: "4K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: true,
        bluetooth: false,
        gps: true,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "AA",
        life: "440 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "1144g",
        dimensions: "109 x 73 x 73 mm",
        color: "Mavi",
      },
    },
    accessories: [
      "Filtre Kitleri",
      "Lens Temizleme Kiti",
      "Yedek Batarya",
      "Ekstra Lens",
      "Tripod",
      "Taşıma Çantası",
    ],
    warranty: "1 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 15,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "2-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: [
      "Kapıda Ödeme",
      "EFT",
      "Banka Havalesi",
      "Kredi Kartı",
      "Kripto Para",
    ],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Morgan Robbins",
        rating: 5,
        comment: "Open sign and something benefit also.",
        date: "2024-03-10",
      },
      {
        author: "Nicholas Lawson",
        rating: 2,
        comment: "Morning water ask.",
        date: "2024-01-31",
      },
      {
        author: "Rachel Baker",
        rating: 5,
        comment: "Size end space admit fall century.",
        date: "2024-01-27",
      },
      {
        author: "Eric Jackson",
        rating: 4,
        comment: "Enter trip camera teacher heavy near.",
        date: "2024-02-16",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Charge management site skill find appear.",
        answer: "Run it well wide whatever deal cut tell.",
        date: "2024-01-19",
      },
      {
        question: "Deal western present else partner attention cost.",
        answer: "A collection forward western answer entire deal.",
        date: "2024-01-17",
      },
      {
        question: "Only fast man commercial.",
        answer: "Campaign road soon act involve surface.",
        date: "2024-02-04",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 42,
    name: "Ürün 42",
    category: "Kişisel Bakım",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 1426.07,
    brand: "Marka j",
    stock: 7,
    ratings: {
      average: 1.6,
      count: 779,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Micro Four Thirds",
      resolution: "12MP",
      videoResolution: "1080p",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: false,
        bluetooth: true,
        gps: true,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "AA",
        life: "655 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "424g",
        dimensions: "115 x 103 x 37 mm",
        color: "Mavi",
      },
    },
    accessories: ["Lens Temizleme Kiti"],
    warranty: "3 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 60,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "3-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: [
      "Kripto Para",
      "Kredi Kartı",
      "Kapıda Ödeme",
      "Banka Havalesi",
    ],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Ashlee Williams",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Wife after garden those long radio sure.",
        date: "2024-03-06",
      },
      {
        author: "James Little",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "It determine new doctor before.",
        date: "2024-02-26",
      },
      {
        author: "Jack Robinson",
        rating: 4,
        comment: "Quality movie operation statement range.",
        date: "2024-03-14",
      },
      {
        author: "John Johns",
        rating: 2,
        comment: "Find to trade experience entire recognize.",
        date: "2024-03-10",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Thing adult act respond program condition which.",
        answer: "President close somebody near data those.",
        date: "2024-01-30",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Consumer happen truth difficult ask production draw special.",
        answer: "Director baby however degree game huge.",
        date: "2024-02-01",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 43,
    name: "Ürün 43",
    category: "Elektronik",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 2233.8,
    brand: "Marka k",
    stock: 19,
    ratings: {
      average: 1.7,
      count: 746,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Full Frame",
      resolution: "55MP",
      videoResolution: "8K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: false,
        bluetooth: false,
        gps: true,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "Li-ion",
        life: "496 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "571g",
        dimensions: "143 x 122 x 67 mm",
        color: "Siyah",
      },
    },
    accessories: [
      "Lens Temizleme Kiti",
      "Taşıma Çantası",
      "Filtre Kitleri",
      "Tripod",
      "Yedek Batarya",
    ],
    warranty: "2 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 30,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "7-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: [
      "Kredi Kartı",
      "EFT",
      "Kapıda Ödeme",
      "Kripto Para",
      "Banka Havalesi",
    ],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Mark Boyer",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Never loss doctor involve one change.",
        date: "2024-01-25",
      },
      {
        author: "Ryan Miller",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Compare fly less term break.",
        date: "2024-01-19",
      },
      {
        author: "Mason Thompson",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Million shake year relationship.",
        date: "2024-01-02",
      },
      {
        author: "Zachary Heath",
        rating: 4,
        comment: "Wind woman bill work head purpose view fill.",
        date: "2024-02-11",
      },
      {
        author: "Catherine Mclaughlin",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "Under total picture important power.",
        date: "2024-02-29",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Article exactly one pay subject.",
        answer: "Shake discussion truth eat.",
        date: "2024-02-08",
      },
      {
        question: "Material north smile deal run.",
        answer: "Million center write whose question side defense.",
        date: "2024-02-07",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 44,
    name: "Ürün 44",
    category: "Kişisel Bakım",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 1806.76,
    brand: "Marka l",
    stock: 88,
    ratings: {
      average: 4.0,
      count: 933,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Full Frame",
      resolution: "22MP",
      videoResolution: "8K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: false,
        bluetooth: true,
        gps: true,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "Li-ion",
        life: "697 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "333g",
        dimensions: "134 x 96 x 95 mm",
        color: "Kırmızı",
      },
    },
    accessories: ["Yedek Batarya", "Tripod", "Filtre Kitleri"],
    warranty: "3 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 15,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "2-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["Kripto Para", "Kredi Kartı"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Tina Beck",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Trouble nice medical expect number.",
        date: "2024-01-16",
      },
      {
        author: "Trevor Ellison",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "Anyone board follow international third blue population.",
        date: "2024-02-14",
      },
      {
        author: "Grant Lewis",
        rating: 2,
        comment: "Over western under three assume field.",
        date: "2024-02-20",
      },
      {
        author: "Jasmin Greer",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "Production example baby help consumer house mean.",
        date: "2024-01-12",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Ever lose should fill.",
        answer: "Even say weight.",
        date: "2024-03-03",
      },
      {
        question: "Sister learn nation list arm key.",
        answer: "Dark team should method ball protect play.",
        date: "2024-01-27",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 45,
    name: "Ürün 45",
    category: "Ev & Yaşam",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 2294.81,
    brand: "Marka m",
    stock: 62,
    ratings: {
      average: 4.8,
      count: 956,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "APS-C",
      resolution: "60MP",
      videoResolution: "8K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: true,
        bluetooth: false,
        gps: false,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "AA",
        life: "418 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "1496g",
        dimensions: "129 x 64 x 77 mm",
        color: "Siyah",
      },
    },
    accessories: ["Yedek Batarya", "Tripod"],
    warranty: "1 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 60,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "5-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["Kapıda Ödeme", "Kripto Para", "EFT"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Matthew Wilson",
        rating: 5,
        comment: "Should buy weight office kitchen run.",
        date: "2024-03-05",
      },
      {
        author: "Veronica Salinas",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Benefit generation include.",
        date: "2024-01-31",
      },
      {
        author: "Ryan Gentry",
        rating: 2,
        comment: "Color husband trouble red into.",
        date: "2024-02-10",
      },
      {
        author: "Paul Blair",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "Attorney stage table land man.",
        date: "2024-01-12",
      },
      {
        author: "Debra Gonzales",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Wonder friend if sound.",
        date: "2024-01-24",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Strong fast hard food hold already.",
        answer: "Wonder speak despite contain stock.",
        date: "2024-02-02",
      },
      {
        question: "Clearly memory factor at feeling training culture.",
        answer: "Heavy part ahead value relationship name throw although.",
        date: "2024-02-23",
      },
      {
        question: "Piece total smile back return.",
        answer: "Push authority little.",
        date: "2024-01-06",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 46,
    name: "Ürün 46",
    category: "Ev & Yaşam",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 432.87,
    brand: "Marka n",
    stock: 21,
    ratings: {
      average: 4.3,
      count: 758,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Micro Four Thirds",
      resolution: "35MP",
      videoResolution: "4K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: true,
        bluetooth: false,
        gps: true,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "Li-ion",
        life: "885 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "502g",
        dimensions: "144 x 106 x 53 mm",
        color: "Mavi",
      },
    },
    accessories: ["Taşıma Çantası"],
    warranty: "1 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 30,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "5-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["Kripto Para", "EFT", "Kredi Kartı"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Mary Medina",
        rating: 4,
        comment: "Lay onto modern record.",
        date: "2024-03-06",
      },
      {
        author: "Ryan Carson",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "Success rather dog newspaper arrive according.",
        date: "2024-03-20",
      },
      {
        author: "Christopher Reilly",
        rating: 5,
        comment: "Type fast above major along important each air.",
        date: "2024-03-20",
      },
      {
        author: "Miranda May",
        rating: 4,
        comment: "Alone station performance poor drop natural.",
        date: "2024-01-28",
      },
      {
        author: "Donald Garcia",
        rating: 5,
        comment: "National question morning various.",
        date: "2024-03-08",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Threat lot PM beautiful.",
        answer: "Pm Congress grow vote scene.",
        date: "2024-01-13",
      },
      {
        question: "Heavy attention understand technology too mother article.",
        answer: "Pass hear oil deal whom nothing toward.",
        date: "2024-03-01",
      },
      {
        question: "Question figure education community director group reach.",
        answer: "Actually her break material like.",
        date: "2024-02-27",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 47,
    name: "Ürün 47",
    category: "Kişisel Bakım",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 1409.94,
    brand: "Marka o",
    stock: 25,
    ratings: {
      average: 4.5,
      count: 466,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "APS-C",
      resolution: "28MP",
      videoResolution: "8K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: false,
        bluetooth: true,
        gps: true,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "AA",
        life: "303 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "1083g",
        dimensions: "146 x 120 x 69 mm",
        color: "Gri",
      },
    },
    accessories: [
      "Filtre Kitleri",
      "Taşıma Çantası",
      "Yedek Batarya",
      "Tripod",
    ],
    warranty: "1 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 60,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "2-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["EFT", "Kredi Kartı"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Michael Rodriguez",
        rating: 5,
        comment:
          "Example responsibility government million cell sure foreign bank.",
        date: "2024-02-02",
      },
      {
        author: "Christine Fisher",
        rating: 5,
        comment: "Eye plant suffer whole.",
        date: "2024-01-08",
      },
      {
        author: "Gregory Thompson",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "Newspaper most know dark pay will.",
        date: "2024-03-08",
      },
      {
        author: "Natalie Taylor",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "Feeling appear garden simple history simple past.",
        date: "2024-01-21",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Trial entire even glass color fly someone.",
        answer: "Look inside teach hope.",
        date: "2024-01-28",
      },
      {
        question: "Begin between station report exist theory head.",
        answer: "Cost garden across decide able.",
        date: "2024-01-22",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 48,
    name: "Ürün 48",
    category: "Kişisel Bakım",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 1355.97,
    brand: "Marka p",
    stock: 8,
    ratings: {
      average: 4.2,
      count: 942,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Full Frame",
      resolution: "55MP",
      videoResolution: "4K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: true,
        bluetooth: true,
        gps: false,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "AA",
        life: "934 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "632g",
        dimensions: "113 x 64 x 84 mm",
        color: "Siyah",
      },
    },
    accessories: ["Yedek Batarya", "Lens Temizleme Kiti", "Ekstra Lens"],
    warranty: "2 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 60,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "1-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["EFT", "Banka Havalesi"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Shawna Diaz",
        rating: 5,
        comment: "Record bill cell walk Democrat.",
        date: "2024-03-07",
      },
      {
        author: "Dylan Sanchez",
        rating: 5,
        comment: "Either old to later person voice door.",
        date: "2024-01-20",
      },
      {
        author: "Elizabeth Holden",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Interest so authority from.",
        date: "2024-03-13",
      },
      {
        author: "Corey Turner",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "Prove event suggest.",
        date: "2024-02-08",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Cultural statement conference from.",
        answer: "Window usually phone age find seven word water.",
        date: "2024-01-24",
      },
      {
        question: "Operation general good opportunity.",
        answer: "Song night each several.",
        date: "2024-01-05",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 49,
    name: "Ürün 49",
    category: "Ev & Yaşam",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 524.63,
    brand: "Marka q",
    stock: 8,
    ratings: {
      average: 3.1,
      count: 247,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Micro Four Thirds",
      resolution: "37MP",
      videoResolution: "1080p",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: true,
        bluetooth: true,
        gps: true,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "AA",
        life: "906 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "1471g",
        dimensions: "143 x 61 x 69 mm",
        color: "Kırmızı",
      },
    },
    accessories: ["Filtre Kitleri", "Lens Temizleme Kiti", "Taşıma Çantası"],
    warranty: "3 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 30,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "2-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["Banka Havalesi", "Kapıda Ödeme", "Kredi Kartı", "EFT"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Anthony Walker",
        rating: 5,
        comment: "Force kitchen assume.",
        date: "2024-02-06",
      },
      {
        author: "Brittany Chapman",
        rating: 5,
        comment: "Piece something arm campaign.",
        date: "2024-02-20",
      },
      {
        author: "Laura Johnson",
        rating: 5,
        comment: "Five employee discover might of.",
        date: "2024-03-14",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Green science test however behind religious discover.",
        answer: "Reduce day catch anything method set product.",
        date: "2024-03-18",
      },
      {
        question: "Mission power somebody technology career tonight act.",
        answer: "Your American plant.",
        date: "2024-02-03",
      },
      {
        question: "Move according begin.",
        answer: "Boy security boy.",
        date: "2024-01-09",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 50,
    name: "Ürün 50",
    category: "Ev & Yaşam",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 3138.1,
    brand: "Marka r",
    stock: 56,
    ratings: {
      average: 4.0,
      count: 850,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "APS-C",
      resolution: "29MP",
      videoResolution: "4K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: false,
        bluetooth: true,
        gps: false,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "AA",
        life: "730 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "941g",
        dimensions: "118 x 121 x 43 mm",
        color: "Mavi",
      },
    },
    accessories: [
      "Filtre Kitleri",
      "Tripod",
      "Yedek Batarya",
      "Taşıma Çantası",
    ],
    warranty: "2 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 60,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "7-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: [
      "Kapıda Ödeme",
      "EFT",
      "Kripto Para",
      "Kredi Kartı",
      "Banka Havalesi",
    ],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Deborah Potts",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "Order how attack public.",
        date: "2024-03-13",
      },
      {
        author: "Carolyn Matthews",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Team step else.",
        date: "2024-02-07",
      },
      {
        author: "Leah Contreras",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Operation book evening buy support model mouth still.",
        date: "2024-01-20",
      },
      {
        author: "Henry Randolph",
        rating: 4,
        comment: "High brother matter democratic property reveal.",
        date: "2024-03-09",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Experience forward detail church up make discuss.",
        answer: "Bring voice wall a memory third beautiful.",
        date: "2024-01-23",
      },
      {
        question: "Front catch music major.",
        answer: "Reflect seat difference manage religious.",
        date: "2024-01-26",
      },
      {
        question: "Knowledge green marriage summer view.",
        answer: "Boy response blood continue opportunity easy inside.",
        date: "2024-01-23",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 51,
    name: "Ürün 51",
    category: "Kişisel Bakım",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 1738.39,
    brand: "Marka s",
    stock: 24,
    ratings: {
      average: 3.9,
      count: 465,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Micro Four Thirds",
      resolution: "57MP",
      videoResolution: "4K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: false,
        bluetooth: false,
        gps: true,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "AA",
        life: "828 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "1362g",
        dimensions: "144 x 71 x 89 mm",
        color: "Siyah",
      },
    },
    accessories: ["Taşıma Çantası", "Tripod"],
    warranty: "2 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 60,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "5-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["Kripto Para"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Cameron Yates",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "South increase doctor sure fast fine.",
        date: "2024-03-10",
      },
      {
        author: "Taylor Green",
        rating: 4,
        comment: "Shoulder result commercial almost.",
        date: "2024-02-28",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Everyone stop career foreign always dog animal.",
        answer: "Series clear give check.",
        date: "2024-01-01",
      },
      {
        question: "Cause decision whatever.",
        answer: "Cultural kind shake state control remember let.",
        date: "2024-02-07",
      },
      {
        question: "Most north agent husband show door.",
        answer: "Hospital than mean book degree rich.",
        date: "2024-03-25",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 52,
    name: "Ürün 52",
    category: "Kişisel Bakım",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 3055.08,
    brand: "Marka t",
    stock: 80,
    ratings: {
      average: 3.9,
      count: 569,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Full Frame",
      resolution: "52MP",
      videoResolution: "4K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: true,
        bluetooth: true,
        gps: false,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "AA",
        life: "900 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "891g",
        dimensions: "104 x 82 x 97 mm",
        color: "Siyah",
      },
    },
    accessories: [
      "Ekstra Lens",
      "Filtre Kitleri",
      "Tripod",
      "Lens Temizleme Kiti",
    ],
    warranty: "1 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 15,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "7-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: [
      "Kapıda Ödeme",
      "Banka Havalesi",
      "Kredi Kartı",
      "EFT",
      "Kripto Para",
    ],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Garrett Jimenez",
        rating: 4,
        comment: "Test spring thus.",
        date: "2024-03-14",
      },
      {
        author: "Nicholas Pope",
        rating: 2,
        comment: "Few film over power about like election.",
        date: "2024-03-18",
      },
      {
        author: "Melanie Miller",
        rating: 4,
        comment: "Control development current wide check leg world.",
        date: "2024-03-18",
      },
      {
        author: "Tyler Castro",
        rating: 2,
        comment: "Attorney for street man.",
        date: "2024-03-11",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Sign expert hotel put wear.",
        answer: "Now series within ok.",
        date: "2024-01-21",
      },
      {
        question: "Degree politics report eye suddenly race.",
        answer: "Drive left drive turn.",
        date: "2024-01-13",
      },
      {
        question: "While treatment least hear teach.",
        answer: "Present tree offer born.",
        date: "2024-02-22",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 53,
    name: "Ürün 53",
    category: "Ev & Yaşam",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 2371.54,
    brand: "Marka u",
    stock: 100,
    ratings: {
      average: 5.0,
      count: 154,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "APS-C",
      resolution: "49MP",
      videoResolution: "4K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: true,
        bluetooth: true,
        gps: true,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "AA",
        life: "721 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "754g",
        dimensions: "148 x 114 x 83 mm",
        color: "Mavi",
      },
    },
    accessories: [
      "Yedek Batarya",
      "Tripod",
      "Lens Temizleme Kiti",
      "Ekstra Lens",
      "Taşıma Çantası",
    ],
    warranty: "2 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 60,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "5-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["EFT", "Banka Havalesi"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "David Rosario",
        rating: 5,
        comment: "Outside beautiful state seat ever.",
        date: "2024-03-10",
      },
      {
        author: "Kimberly Wade",
        rating: 4,
        comment: "Phone vote these.",
        date: "2024-01-30",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Product back lay administration happy probably.",
        answer: "Ask she likely.",
        date: "2024-01-02",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 54,
    name: "Ürün 54",
    category: "Ev & Yaşam",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 984.38,
    brand: "Marka v",
    stock: 32,
    ratings: {
      average: 1.7,
      count: 401,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "APS-C",
      resolution: "43MP",
      videoResolution: "4K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: false,
        bluetooth: false,
        gps: false,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "Li-ion",
        life: "525 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "467g",
        dimensions: "110 x 87 x 70 mm",
        color: "Siyah",
      },
    },
    accessories: ["Lens Temizleme Kiti", "Ekstra Lens", "Filtre Kitleri"],
    warranty: "1 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 15,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "5-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: [
      "EFT",
      "Kredi Kartı",
      "Kapıda Ödeme",
      "Banka Havalesi",
      "Kripto Para",
    ],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Charles Bradley",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Wife every free between indeed board green.",
        date: "2024-01-02",
      },
      {
        author: "Brian Dunn",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Ever dark method.",
        date: "2024-03-12",
      },
      {
        author: "Monica Key DDS",
        rating: 4,
        comment: "Guy over side.",
        date: "2024-02-07",
      },
      {
        author: "Jordan Duran",
        rating: 4,
        comment: "Oil including industry draw friend interest cause.",
        date: "2024-03-05",
      },
      {
        author: "Robert Sampson",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "Push some growth small.",
        date: "2024-02-22",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Baby all in brother store model technology.",
        answer: "Perform start early game group section say capital.",
        date: "2024-03-10",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 55,
    name: "Ürün 55",
    category: "Kişisel Bakım",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 2898.17,
    brand: "Marka w",
    stock: 28,
    ratings: {
      average: 3.3,
      count: 689,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Full Frame",
      resolution: "34MP",
      videoResolution: "4K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: false,
        bluetooth: true,
        gps: true,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "Li-ion",
        life: "309 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "414g",
        dimensions: "107 x 79 x 73 mm",
        color: "Siyah",
      },
    },
    accessories: [
      "Yedek Batarya",
      "Ekstra Lens",
      "Filtre Kitleri",
      "Tripod",
      "Lens Temizleme Kiti",
      "Taşıma Çantası",
    ],
    warranty: "3 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 60,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "1-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: [
      "EFT",
      "Banka Havalesi",
      "Kredi Kartı",
      "Kripto Para",
      "Kapıda Ödeme",
    ],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Jonathan Hansen",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "Go relate experience easy last company child.",
        date: "2024-01-14",
      },
      {
        author: "Micheal Cole",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "He feeling executive success design receive.",
        date: "2024-03-19",
      },
      {
        author: "Tracy Hunter",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "Edge necessary free sure.",
        date: "2024-03-16",
      },
      {
        author: "Mr. Matthew Lopez",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "Task these begin employee ever program.",
        date: "2024-03-10",
      },
      {
        author: "Mary Holt",
        rating: 4,
        comment: "Top traditional him friend collection.",
        date: "2024-01-24",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Toward image too.",
        answer: "Seem us cultural front plant benefit actually film.",
        date: "2024-01-31",
      },
      {
        question: "Him when authority site TV stock.",
        answer: "Big interview manage many administration listen water.",
        date: "2024-02-16",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 56,
    name: "Ürün 56",
    category: "Ev & Yaşam",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 1362.46,
    brand: "Marka x",
    stock: 62,
    ratings: {
      average: 1.9,
      count: 220,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Full Frame",
      resolution: "31MP",
      videoResolution: "1080p",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: true,
        bluetooth: true,
        gps: true,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "AA",
        life: "512 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "326g",
        dimensions: "141 x 114 x 85 mm",
        color: "Siyah",
      },
    },
    accessories: [
      "Yedek Batarya",
      "Filtre Kitleri",
      "Taşıma Çantası",
      "Tripod",
      "Ekstra Lens",
      "Lens Temizleme Kiti",
    ],
    warranty: "1 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 30,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "1-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["Kredi Kartı"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Courtney Dudley",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Friend religious wind.",
        date: "2024-03-24",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Myself its international three fine ever.",
        answer: "Wall hotel artist discover certain.",
        date: "2024-02-18",
      },
      {
        question: "Base something physical agreement sound.",
        answer: "Those forward former.",
        date: "2024-01-24",
      },
      {
        question: "It early girl wrong trip clearly.",
        answer: "Course campaign girl.",
        date: "2024-02-26",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 57,
    name: "Ürün 57",
    category: "Ev & Yaşam",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 1487.63,
    brand: "Marka y",
    stock: 83,
    ratings: {
      average: 2.2,
      count: 713,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Micro Four Thirds",
      resolution: "46MP",
      videoResolution: "4K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: true,
        bluetooth: true,
        gps: true,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "AA",
        life: "609 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "855g",
        dimensions: "150 x 106 x 33 mm",
        color: "Gri",
      },
    },
    accessories: [
      "Yedek Batarya",
      "Filtre Kitleri",
      "Lens Temizleme Kiti",
      "Ekstra Lens",
    ],
    warranty: "1 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 30,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "3-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["EFT", "Banka Havalesi"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Andrea Lowe",
        rating: 5,
        comment: "Situation group benefit consumer.",
        date: "2024-02-11",
      },
      {
        author: "Johnny Terry",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Score eye difference front but compare.",
        date: "2024-02-08",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Court fight food finish.",
        answer: "Between situation eye put.",
        date: "2024-03-22",
      },
      {
        question: "Modern read film push home.",
        answer: "Admit official certain indeed.",
        date: "2024-03-05",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 58,
    name: "Ürün 58",
    category: "Ev & Yaşam",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 659.99,
    brand: "Marka z",
    stock: 78,
    ratings: {
      average: 3.8,
      count: 793,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "APS-C",
      resolution: "13MP",
      videoResolution: "1080p",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: true,
        bluetooth: false,
        gps: true,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "AA",
        life: "424 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "1133g",
        dimensions: "100 x 81 x 53 mm",
        color: "Siyah",
      },
    },
    accessories: [
      "Filtre Kitleri",
      "Ekstra Lens",
      "Lens Temizleme Kiti",
      "Yedek Batarya",
      "Tripod",
      "Taşıma Çantası",
    ],
    warranty: "1 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 15,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "2-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["Kapıda Ödeme", "Kredi Kartı"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Anthony Richards",
        rating: 5,
        comment: "Civil offer trial night sign through enjoy interview.",
        date: "2024-01-22",
      },
      {
        author: "Stephanie Carr",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Issue police usually change visit day.",
        date: "2024-03-07",
      },
      {
        author: "Jeffrey Villarreal",
        rating: 4,
        comment: "Approach watch significant strong Congress.",
        date: "2024-01-03",
      },
      {
        author: "Jaime Hall",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "Own one walk.",
        date: "2024-01-16",
      },
      {
        author: "Mrs. Margaret Parker",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "So easy require anything better nice.",
        date: "2024-02-08",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Design might some.",
        answer: "Good professor church piece religious.",
        date: "2024-02-07",
      },
      {
        question: "Page customer behavior ability page peace executive.",
        answer: "Home film development process foreign.",
        date: "2024-01-31",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 59,
    name: "Ürün 59",
    category: "Ev & Yaşam",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 3729.06,
    brand: "Marka {",
    stock: 96,
    ratings: {
      average: 3.2,
      count: 111,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Full Frame",
      resolution: "18MP",
      videoResolution: "4K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: true,
        bluetooth: false,
        gps: false,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "Li-ion",
        life: "423 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "1146g",
        dimensions: "124 x 122 x 72 mm",
        color: "Mavi",
      },
    },
    accessories: [
      "Filtre Kitleri",
      "Lens Temizleme Kiti",
      "Ekstra Lens",
      "Yedek Batarya",
      "Taşıma Çantası",
      "Tripod",
    ],
    warranty: "1 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 15,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "2-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: [
      "Kripto Para",
      "Kredi Kartı",
      "Banka Havalesi",
      "Kapıda Ödeme",
      "EFT",
    ],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Anthony Johnson",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Sense she feeling off country.",
        date: "2024-01-19",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Article seat history magazine.",
        answer: "Job article real where friend live.",
        date: "2024-01-27",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 60,
    name: "Ürün 60",
    category: "Elektronik",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 1677.41,
    brand: "Marka |",
    stock: 37,
    ratings: {
      average: 3.1,
      count: 73,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "APS-C",
      resolution: "58MP",
      videoResolution: "1080p",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: false,
        bluetooth: true,
        gps: true,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "AA",
        life: "806 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "512g",
        dimensions: "118 x 124 x 57 mm",
        color: "Siyah",
      },
    },
    accessories: ["Taşıma Çantası"],
    warranty: "3 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 15,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "1-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: [
      "Banka Havalesi",
      "Kripto Para",
      "EFT",
      "Kredi Kartı",
      "Kapıda Ödeme",
    ],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Mr. Thomas Rodriguez",
        rating: 4,
        comment: "She inside hard create probably.",
        date: "2024-03-22",
      },
      {
        author: "Jason Nelson",
        rating: 2,
        comment: "Fight police suggest rise later us.",
        date: "2024-01-25",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Similar response throughout me see sure.",
        answer: "Beat among work which feel candidate key between.",
        date: "2024-02-08",
      },
      {
        question: "Pattern dream late conference toward although.",
        answer: "Occur recognize exist them attention arrive from so.",
        date: "2024-01-06",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 61,
    name: "Ürün 61",
    category: "Kişisel Bakım",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 1542.16,
    brand: "Marka }",
    stock: 19,
    ratings: {
      average: 2.1,
      count: 302,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Micro Four Thirds",
      resolution: "46MP",
      videoResolution: "4K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: false,
        bluetooth: true,
        gps: true,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "Li-ion",
        life: "889 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "309g",
        dimensions: "136 x 120 x 31 mm",
        color: "Mavi",
      },
    },
    accessories: ["Taşıma Çantası"],
    warranty: "1 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 15,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "1-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["Banka Havalesi", "Kripto Para"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Scott Buchanan II",
        rating: 5,
        comment: "A letter control prevent book manager.",
        date: "2024-01-02",
      },
      {
        author: "Destiny Wells",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Read about police pay third indicate director.",
        date: "2024-02-12",
      },
      {
        author: "Patricia Holland",
        rating: 4,
        comment: "Middle run job without large into personal five.",
        date: "2024-03-05",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Go move boy million perhaps industry art.",
        answer: "Along other employee possible win case with contain.",
        date: "2024-01-25",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 62,
    name: "Ürün 62",
    category: "Elektronik",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 2648.03,
    brand: "Marka ~",
    stock: 66,
    ratings: {
      average: 4.5,
      count: 239,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Micro Four Thirds",
      resolution: "14MP",
      videoResolution: "8K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: true,
        bluetooth: true,
        gps: true,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "AA",
        life: "412 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "611g",
        dimensions: "118 x 101 x 35 mm",
        color: "Siyah",
      },
    },
    accessories: [
      "Lens Temizleme Kiti",
      "Yedek Batarya",
      "Taşıma Çantası",
      "Ekstra Lens",
      "Filtre Kitleri",
    ],
    warranty: "2 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 15,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "5-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: [
      "EFT",
      "Banka Havalesi",
      "Kripto Para",
      "Kredi Kartı",
      "Kapıda Ödeme",
    ],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Lucas Gross",
        rating: 2,
        comment: "Scene happen the develop space benefit choose.",
        date: "2024-01-16",
      },
      {
        author: "Edward Barnett",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "Also range popular military free authority.",
        date: "2024-01-01",
      },
      {
        author: "Catherine Freeman",
        rating: 4,
        comment: "Interview possible no realize.",
        date: "2024-03-14",
      },
      {
        author: "Jordan Powell",
        rating: 4,
        comment: "Blue least nice whose.",
        date: "2024-02-11",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Cut door focus young real.",
        answer: "Cell begin themselves include take or.",
        date: "2024-01-27",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 63,
    name: "Ürün 63",
    category: "Elektronik",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 1921.5,
    brand: "Marka ",
    stock: 36,
    ratings: {
      average: 2.1,
      count: 588,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Micro Four Thirds",
      resolution: "37MP",
      videoResolution: "4K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: false,
        bluetooth: true,
        gps: false,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "AA",
        life: "599 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "863g",
        dimensions: "107 x 93 x 64 mm",
        color: "Kırmızı",
      },
    },
    accessories: [
      "Filtre Kitleri",
      "Yedek Batarya",
      "Taşıma Çantası",
      "Lens Temizleme Kiti",
      "Ekstra Lens",
      "Tripod",
    ],
    warranty: "1 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 30,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "2-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: [
      "Kredi Kartı",
      "Banka Havalesi",
      "Kapıda Ödeme",
      "EFT",
      "Kripto Para",
    ],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Deborah Gonzalez",
        rating: 5,
        comment: "Set human himself tell.",
        date: "2024-03-14",
      },
      {
        author: "Megan Stanton",
        rating: 4,
        comment: "Tell alone interesting painting.",
        date: "2024-03-06",
      },
      {
        author: "Juan Velasquez",
        rating: 5,
        comment: "Off remember assume bag even edge.",
        date: "2024-01-30",
      },
      {
        author: "Nancy King",
        rating: 2,
        comment: "Attention quite office painting machine.",
        date: "2024-01-21",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Manager question mind light boy.",
        answer: "Firm word establish hit each another key.",
        date: "2024-03-12",
      },
      {
        question: "Price culture lead sometimes interest before.",
        answer: "Get sit civil we.",
        date: "2024-02-15",
      },
      {
        question: "Help contain on picture kitchen high hard.",
        answer: "Everybody necessary run above.",
        date: "2024-03-17",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 64,
    name: "Ürün 64",
    category: "Ev & Yaşam",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 1463.17,
    brand: "Marka ",
    stock: 66,
    ratings: {
      average: 2.1,
      count: 20,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Full Frame",
      resolution: "14MP",
      videoResolution: "8K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: false,
        bluetooth: true,
        gps: false,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "Li-ion",
        life: "628 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "465g",
        dimensions: "101 x 106 x 50 mm",
        color: "Gri",
      },
    },
    accessories: [
      "Yedek Batarya",
      "Filtre Kitleri",
      "Taşıma Çantası",
      "Lens Temizleme Kiti",
      "Ekstra Lens",
    ],
    warranty: "3 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 60,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "1-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: [
      "Kredi Kartı",
      "Banka Havalesi",
      "Kapıda Ödeme",
      "Kripto Para",
    ],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "David Steele",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Both way mean type of thus but crime.",
        date: "2024-01-16",
      },
      {
        author: "Luke Russo",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Good mind question.",
        date: "2024-03-23",
      },
      {
        author: "Donna Wright",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Television serious expect fight.",
        date: "2024-01-24",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Up road note ten.",
        answer: "Full national reflect someone.",
        date: "2024-03-10",
      },
      {
        question: "Maybe room so Republican trade.",
        answer: "Thank something claim federal local building move outside.",
        date: "2024-01-26",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 65,
    name: "Ürün 65",
    category: "Ev & Yaşam",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 3191.6,
    brand: "Marka ",
    stock: 31,
    ratings: {
      average: 3.8,
      count: 898,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Full Frame",
      resolution: "38MP",
      videoResolution: "8K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: false,
        bluetooth: true,
        gps: true,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "Li-ion",
        life: "460 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "401g",
        dimensions: "113 x 73 x 33 mm",
        color: "Siyah",
      },
    },
    accessories: [
      "Ekstra Lens",
      "Filtre Kitleri",
      "Lens Temizleme Kiti",
      "Tripod",
      "Taşıma Çantası",
    ],
    warranty: "2 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 30,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "2-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["EFT", "Banka Havalesi"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Brittany Hunt",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "Above interview safe it its guess surface.",
        date: "2024-01-06",
      },
      {
        author: "Debra Williamson",
        rating: 2,
        comment: "Executive help carry far situation hear experience.",
        date: "2024-01-03",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Mr discover glass industry international door then.",
        answer: "Would religious start man mind hospital.",
        date: "2024-03-09",
      },
      {
        question: "Character step notice commercial.",
        answer: "Artist dinner collection season according reason.",
        date: "2024-03-22",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 66,
    name: "Ürün 66",
    category: "Ev & Yaşam",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 2696.61,
    brand: "Marka ",
    stock: 38,
    ratings: {
      average: 2.3,
      count: 879,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Micro Four Thirds",
      resolution: "24MP",
      videoResolution: "4K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: true,
        bluetooth: false,
        gps: true,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "AA",
        life: "465 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "953g",
        dimensions: "120 x 103 x 68 mm",
        color: "Mavi",
      },
    },
    accessories: [
      "Tripod",
      "Filtre Kitleri",
      "Taşıma Çantası",
      "Ekstra Lens",
      "Lens Temizleme Kiti",
    ],
    warranty: "3 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 60,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "2-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["Kredi Kartı", "Kripto Para", "EFT", "Kapıda Ödeme"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Laurie Larson",
        rating: 5,
        comment: "Performance among stock myself population day large.",
        date: "2024-02-16",
      },
      {
        author: "Bryan Smith",
        rating: 5,
        comment: "Hope enjoy admit.",
        date: "2024-01-06",
      },
      {
        author: "Patricia Morales",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "White thus computer ask by thank continue.",
        date: "2024-03-04",
      },
      {
        author: "Ashley Harmon",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "Until successful game produce yeah while letter.",
        date: "2024-03-18",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Pretty wide close financial serious deep huge remain.",
        answer: "Note growth operation such threat tax.",
        date: "2024-02-12",
      },
      {
        question: "Success American then put whom usually.",
        answer: "Two allow third realize discover glass away.",
        date: "2024-02-14",
      },
      {
        question: "Again war measure them green real.",
        answer: "Drive effort floor focus house place.",
        date: "2024-03-07",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 67,
    name: "Ürün 67",
    category: "Kişisel Bakım",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 3599.58,
    brand: "Marka ",
    stock: 2,
    ratings: {
      average: 3.7,
      count: 205,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Micro Four Thirds",
      resolution: "38MP",
      videoResolution: "8K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: false,
        bluetooth: false,
        gps: false,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "Li-ion",
        life: "507 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "412g",
        dimensions: "101 x 85 x 42 mm",
        color: "Siyah",
      },
    },
    accessories: ["Taşıma Çantası", "Ekstra Lens", "Tripod"],
    warranty: "3 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 60,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "1-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: [
      "Kripto Para",
      "Kapıda Ödeme",
      "Banka Havalesi",
      "EFT",
      "Kredi Kartı",
    ],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Ronald Swanson",
        rating: 4,
        comment: "Unit call consider.",
        date: "2024-01-25",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Prepare detail own value fund you century.",
        answer: "Save happy social often though than.",
        date: "2024-03-09",
      },
      {
        question: "Size because plant apply.",
        answer: "Middle all gun guess various family.",
        date: "2024-01-02",
      },
      {
        question: "Economic be blue hour be your view whom.",
        answer: "Real top find leader its generation oil.",
        date: "2024-01-10",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 68,
    name: "Ürün 68",
    category: "Elektronik",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 1415.39,
    brand: "Marka ",
    stock: 13,
    ratings: {
      average: 2.8,
      count: 691,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Micro Four Thirds",
      resolution: "34MP",
      videoResolution: "1080p",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: false,
        bluetooth: true,
        gps: true,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "Li-ion",
        life: "926 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "1249g",
        dimensions: "134 x 100 x 88 mm",
        color: "Kırmızı",
      },
    },
    accessories: [
      "Filtre Kitleri",
      "Lens Temizleme Kiti",
      "Ekstra Lens",
      "Taşıma Çantası",
      "Yedek Batarya",
      "Tripod",
    ],
    warranty: "3 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 15,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "2-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["EFT", "Banka Havalesi"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "George Bates",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Travel teacher other great save.",
        date: "2024-01-27",
      },
      {
        author: "Joel Wiley",
        rating: 5,
        comment: "Yes training bit wife which.",
        date: "2024-01-21",
      },
      {
        author: "Joshua Patterson",
        rating: 2,
        comment: "Pass production bag our.",
        date: "2024-02-21",
      },
      {
        author: "Mary Barnes",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "People explain century.",
        date: "2024-02-17",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Religious support kid next.",
        answer: "Artist film doctor buy offer important.",
        date: "2024-02-11",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 69,
    name: "Ürün 69",
    category: "Kişisel Bakım",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 1750.08,
    brand: "Marka ",
    stock: 39,
    ratings: {
      average: 3.6,
      count: 561,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Full Frame",
      resolution: "55MP",
      videoResolution: "4K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: false,
        bluetooth: false,
        gps: false,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "AA",
        life: "472 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "489g",
        dimensions: "137 x 61 x 60 mm",
        color: "Kırmızı",
      },
    },
    accessories: ["Yedek Batarya"],
    warranty: "1 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 30,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "3-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: [
      "Kripto Para",
      "EFT",
      "Kredi Kartı",
      "Kapıda Ödeme",
      "Banka Havalesi",
    ],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Patrick Hernandez",
        rating: 2,
        comment: "Mrs hour expert others.",
        date: "2024-03-07",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Happy would matter.",
        answer: "Moment main develop trip artist figure less.",
        date: "2024-03-21",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 70,
    name: "Ürün 70",
    category: "Ev & Yaşam",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 4835.65,
    brand: "Marka ",
    stock: 61,
    ratings: {
      average: 4.9,
      count: 889,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Micro Four Thirds",
      resolution: "22MP",
      videoResolution: "8K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: true,
        bluetooth: false,
        gps: true,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "Li-ion",
        life: "575 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "662g",
        dimensions: "146 x 117 x 98 mm",
        color: "Gri",
      },
    },
    accessories: ["Taşıma Çantası"],
    warranty: "1 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 60,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "2-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["Kapıda Ödeme"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Sherry Edwards",
        rating: 5,
        comment: "If blood deep audience.",
        date: "2024-02-08",
      },
      {
        author: "Amy Williams",
        rating: 2,
        comment: "Against hand play.",
        date: "2024-01-14",
      },
      {
        author: "Randy Davis",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "Top ever example cover company.",
        date: "2024-02-27",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          "Establish program talk learn serious recognize reflect loss.",
        answer: "Individual arm sit.",
        date: "2024-02-26",
      },
      {
        question: "Memory region provide forward main player.",
        answer: "Clearly red guy travel rise nor.",
        date: "2024-02-10",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 71,
    name: "Ürün 71",
    category: "Ev & Yaşam",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 3658.74,
    brand: "Marka ",
    stock: 21,
    ratings: {
      average: 3.7,
      count: 683,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Full Frame",
      resolution: "46MP",
      videoResolution: "8K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: false,
        bluetooth: false,
        gps: false,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "AA",
        life: "644 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "1456g",
        dimensions: "126 x 104 x 62 mm",
        color: "Kırmızı",
      },
    },
    accessories: ["Yedek Batarya"],
    warranty: "2 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 60,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "7-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: [
      "Kapıda Ödeme",
      "Banka Havalesi",
      "EFT",
      "Kripto Para",
      "Kredi Kartı",
    ],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Michael Ward",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Travel woman provide college couple two reason entire.",
        date: "2024-03-15",
      },
      {
        author: "Lori Solomon",
        rating: 2,
        comment: "Charge here here candidate.",
        date: "2024-01-05",
      },
      {
        author: "Daniel Colon",
        rating: 4,
        comment: "Pm bad image seat current lead should.",
        date: "2024-01-10",
      },
      {
        author: "Jonathan Jimenez",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Grow fear organization its somebody message.",
        date: "2024-03-15",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Major take floor open base director.",
        answer: "Suddenly morning event matter everybody produce bring.",
        date: "2024-01-20",
      },
      {
        question: "Environmental her pretty clearly travel drug.",
        answer: "Line front certainly reveal wrong turn follow.",
        date: "2024-03-18",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 72,
    name: "Ürün 72",
    category: "Ev & Yaşam",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 3507.99,
    brand: "Marka ",
    stock: 94,
    ratings: {
      average: 1.9,
      count: 404,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "APS-C",
      resolution: "16MP",
      videoResolution: "4K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: true,
        bluetooth: false,
        gps: false,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "AA",
        life: "740 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "342g",
        dimensions: "140 x 89 x 85 mm",
        color: "Kırmızı",
      },
    },
    accessories: ["Ekstra Lens", "Filtre Kitleri"],
    warranty: "1 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 30,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "1-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["Kapıda Ödeme", "EFT", "Kripto Para", "Banka Havalesi"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Jeffrey Morgan",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Employee lead action either religious continue.",
        date: "2024-02-09",
      },
      {
        author: "Cheyenne Morris",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Wish couple professor fact.",
        date: "2024-03-18",
      },
      {
        author: "Denise Foster",
        rating: 2,
        comment: "Deep few concern hundred.",
        date: "2024-03-05",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Other series product kind if.",
        answer: "Discuss finally point very dream.",
        date: "2024-02-18",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 73,
    name: "Ürün 73",
    category: "Kişisel Bakım",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 3801.27,
    brand: "Marka ",
    stock: 22,
    ratings: {
      average: 3.2,
      count: 106,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "APS-C",
      resolution: "29MP",
      videoResolution: "4K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: false,
        bluetooth: false,
        gps: false,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "AA",
        life: "307 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "339g",
        dimensions: "147 x 69 x 54 mm",
        color: "Kırmızı",
      },
    },
    accessories: ["Tripod"],
    warranty: "3 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 15,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "7-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["Kredi Kartı", "EFT", "Kripto Para", "Kapıda Ödeme"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Christina Berry",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Career store bit computer.",
        date: "2024-03-11",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Law focus evidence partner.",
        answer: "Also case show trial event job.",
        date: "2024-03-22",
      },
      {
        question: "Concern red state yeah home.",
        answer: "Sister late house car far benefit.",
        date: "2024-02-03",
      },
      {
        question: "Box provide threat send soldier wind.",
        answer: "Specific entire onto.",
        date: "2024-03-21",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 74,
    name: "Ürün 74",
    category: "Kişisel Bakım",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 2187.77,
    brand: "Marka ",
    stock: 50,
    ratings: {
      average: 2.5,
      count: 595,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Micro Four Thirds",
      resolution: "48MP",
      videoResolution: "1080p",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: true,
        bluetooth: true,
        gps: false,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "Li-ion",
        life: "896 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "685g",
        dimensions: "125 x 110 x 42 mm",
        color: "Mavi",
      },
    },
    accessories: ["Yedek Batarya"],
    warranty: "3 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 30,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "2-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["Kapıda Ödeme", "Kripto Para"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Matthew Hubbard",
        rating: 2,
        comment: "Newspaper develop pay hair.",
        date: "2024-03-11",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Reason open cultural.",
        answer: "Left deep language risk present exist.",
        date: "2024-01-11",
      },
      {
        question: "Beautiful over just government.",
        answer: "Industry billion eye top level eight ground Mr.",
        date: "2024-03-23",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 75,
    name: "Ürün 75",
    category: "Ev & Yaşam",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 2416.72,
    brand: "Marka ",
    stock: 96,
    ratings: {
      average: 2.3,
      count: 364,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "APS-C",
      resolution: "29MP",
      videoResolution: "8K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: true,
        bluetooth: true,
        gps: false,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "AA",
        life: "589 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "1238g",
        dimensions: "148 x 104 x 99 mm",
        color: "Mavi",
      },
    },
    accessories: [
      "Lens Temizleme Kiti",
      "Taşıma Çantası",
      "Ekstra Lens",
      "Filtre Kitleri",
      "Tripod",
    ],
    warranty: "3 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 15,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "2-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["EFT"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Martha Turner",
        rating: 4,
        comment: "Information walk from walk put item put whether.",
        date: "2024-01-08",
      },
      {
        author: "Todd Lewis",
        rating: 2,
        comment: "Boy personal meeting keep read various.",
        date: "2024-03-16",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Color military loss morning.",
        answer: "Feel cause heavy baby happen story.",
        date: "2024-03-07",
      },
      {
        question: "Build media traditional.",
        answer: "Cell director lot hotel two.",
        date: "2024-01-10",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 76,
    name: "Ürün 76",
    category: "Elektronik",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 4397.61,
    brand: "Marka ",
    stock: 13,
    ratings: {
      average: 2.8,
      count: 570,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Full Frame",
      resolution: "53MP",
      videoResolution: "1080p",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: true,
        bluetooth: false,
        gps: false,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "AA",
        life: "410 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "1138g",
        dimensions: "133 x 79 x 73 mm",
        color: "Kırmızı",
      },
    },
    accessories: ["Taşıma Çantası"],
    warranty: "3 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 30,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "2-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: [
      "Kripto Para",
      "EFT",
      "Banka Havalesi",
      "Kapıda Ödeme",
      "Kredi Kartı",
    ],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Justin Webb",
        rating: 2,
        comment: "Face citizen hour similar his.",
        date: "2024-02-24",
      },
      {
        author: "Claire Cherry",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Increase difficult term allow tough example feeling.",
        date: "2024-02-25",
      },
      {
        author: "Emma Sloan",
        rating: 4,
        comment: "Real red pretty write.",
        date: "2024-03-23",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Material do against action court girl exist.",
        answer: "Base reveal stand despite story force necessary work.",
        date: "2024-01-30",
      },
      {
        question: "Bad pretty method alone.",
        answer: "Ever huge school arm.",
        date: "2024-03-18",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 77,
    name: "Ürün 77",
    category: "Ev & Yaşam",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 1713.5,
    brand: "Marka ",
    stock: 94,
    ratings: {
      average: 4.7,
      count: 930,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Micro Four Thirds",
      resolution: "27MP",
      videoResolution: "4K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: false,
        bluetooth: false,
        gps: false,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "AA",
        life: "501 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "1288g",
        dimensions: "112 x 115 x 83 mm",
        color: "Kırmızı",
      },
    },
    accessories: [
      "Taşıma Çantası",
      "Yedek Batarya",
      "Tripod",
      "Lens Temizleme Kiti",
    ],
    warranty: "1 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 15,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "3-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: [
      "EFT",
      "Kapıda Ödeme",
      "Banka Havalesi",
      "Kripto Para",
      "Kredi Kartı",
    ],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Melissa Lee",
        rating: 5,
        comment:
          "Avoid majority computer kitchen information relate production receive.",
        date: "2024-03-08",
      },
      {
        author: "Michael White",
        rating: 5,
        comment: "Image partner understand get.",
        date: "2024-03-20",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Probably TV over specific remember often.",
        answer: "Democrat recently beyond discover out career property.",
        date: "2024-01-11",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 78,
    name: "Ürün 78",
    category: "Ev & Yaşam",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 3032.77,
    brand: "Marka ",
    stock: 88,
    ratings: {
      average: 2.9,
      count: 811,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Micro Four Thirds",
      resolution: "37MP",
      videoResolution: "1080p",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: false,
        bluetooth: true,
        gps: true,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "AA",
        life: "970 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "1276g",
        dimensions: "120 x 103 x 82 mm",
        color: "Gri",
      },
    },
    accessories: ["Filtre Kitleri", "Tripod", "Ekstra Lens", "Taşıma Çantası"],
    warranty: "2 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 15,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "7-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: [
      "Kapıda Ödeme",
      "Banka Havalesi",
      "Kredi Kartı",
      "EFT",
      "Kripto Para",
    ],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Michael Davis",
        rating: 4,
        comment: "Write wrong here wait effect anything cell watch.",
        date: "2024-02-23",
      },
      {
        author: "Tiffany Mccarthy",
        rating: 4,
        comment:
          "Guess response throughout enjoy interview third authority wall.",
        date: "2024-01-19",
      },
      {
        author: "Brent Rogers",
        rating: 5,
        comment: "Lose door hit response wonder.",
        date: "2024-01-06",
      },
      {
        author: "Zachary Carey",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Campaign win record star dinner.",
        date: "2024-01-14",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Admit night least company letter scene measure.",
        answer: "Them measure itself off boy lead.",
        date: "2024-02-14",
      },
      {
        question: "Age degree institution our although.",
        answer: "Risk story customer child recently hold.",
        date: "2024-01-15",
      },
      {
        question: "Address on chance successful Democrat marriage.",
        answer: "Everybody identify understand customer.",
        date: "2024-02-07",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 79,
    name: "Ürün 79",
    category: "Elektronik",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 2410.25,
    brand: "Marka ",
    stock: 78,
    ratings: {
      average: 3.4,
      count: 347,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "APS-C",
      resolution: "50MP",
      videoResolution: "4K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: false,
        bluetooth: true,
        gps: false,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "AA",
        life: "869 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "1360g",
        dimensions: "104 x 76 x 56 mm",
        color: "Mavi",
      },
    },
    accessories: [
      "Yedek Batarya",
      "Filtre Kitleri",
      "Lens Temizleme Kiti",
      "Ekstra Lens",
      "Taşıma Çantası",
    ],
    warranty: "2 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 60,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "7-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: [
      "Banka Havalesi",
      "Kripto Para",
      "EFT",
      "Kapıda Ödeme",
      "Kredi Kartı",
    ],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Kathleen Donovan",
        rating: 4,
        comment: "Far though actually.",
        date: "2024-03-22",
      },
      {
        author: "Douglas Andrews",
        rating: 2,
        comment: "Culture pressure tend on card until evidence.",
        date: "2024-03-21",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Simply safe administration amount.",
        answer: "Box under need other.",
        date: "2024-02-21",
      },
      {
        question: "Sound when make drive part force.",
        answer: "Yeah suddenly student fear suffer everybody fear amount.",
        date: "2024-03-20",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 80,
    name: "Ürün 80",
    category: "Elektronik",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 2756.93,
    brand: "Marka ",
    stock: 53,
    ratings: {
      average: 3.3,
      count: 817,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "APS-C",
      resolution: "40MP",
      videoResolution: "1080p",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: false,
        bluetooth: true,
        gps: false,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "Li-ion",
        life: "345 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "544g",
        dimensions: "119 x 68 x 93 mm",
        color: "Kırmızı",
      },
    },
    accessories: ["Filtre Kitleri", "Tripod", "Ekstra Lens"],
    warranty: "3 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 30,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "2-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["Banka Havalesi", "Kredi Kartı"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Lindsay Williamson",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "Fear center so prove wind explain top.",
        date: "2024-03-03",
      },
      {
        author: "Melody Wilson",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Ever race bit perhaps off window child station.",
        date: "2024-03-25",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Realize strategy article would.",
        answer: "Cut through official not program box check.",
        date: "2024-03-13",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 81,
    name: "Ürün 81",
    category: "Kişisel Bakım",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 3874.77,
    brand: "Marka ",
    stock: 77,
    ratings: {
      average: 2.6,
      count: 827,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "APS-C",
      resolution: "38MP",
      videoResolution: "1080p",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: false,
        bluetooth: false,
        gps: false,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "AA",
        life: "1000 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "919g",
        dimensions: "108 x 119 x 49 mm",
        color: "Siyah",
      },
    },
    accessories: ["Taşıma Çantası", "Filtre Kitleri", "Ekstra Lens"],
    warranty: "2 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 60,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "2-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["Banka Havalesi", "Kredi Kartı", "EFT"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Erin Morales",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "On learn will old.",
        date: "2024-03-24",
      },
      {
        author: "Nicole Hernandez",
        rating: 4,
        comment: "Mind until total nor follow it type.",
        date: "2024-03-02",
      },
      {
        author: "Christie Smith",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Force character service worry Democrat yourself establish.",
        date: "2024-01-08",
      },
      {
        author: "Victoria Singleton",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Involve science law answer near military join.",
        date: "2024-01-23",
      },
      {
        author: "Dawn Myers",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Exist production impact society set might back professional.",
        date: "2024-01-03",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Live into best close case detail.",
        answer: "Recognize knowledge task food either whether.",
        date: "2024-03-22",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 82,
    name: "Ürün 82",
    category: "Kişisel Bakım",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 358.93,
    brand: "Marka ",
    stock: 81,
    ratings: {
      average: 2.7,
      count: 731,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "APS-C",
      resolution: "13MP",
      videoResolution: "1080p",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: false,
        bluetooth: false,
        gps: false,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "Li-ion",
        life: "418 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "689g",
        dimensions: "116 x 115 x 51 mm",
        color: "Kırmızı",
      },
    },
    accessories: ["Ekstra Lens", "Yedek Batarya"],
    warranty: "1 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 15,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "3-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: [
      "Kredi Kartı",
      "Banka Havalesi",
      "EFT",
      "Kapıda Ödeme",
      "Kripto Para",
    ],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Joshua Spencer",
        rating: 5,
        comment: "Product significant every speak world nothing.",
        date: "2024-02-26",
      },
      {
        author: "Michael Mendoza",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Lose back company good meeting.",
        date: "2024-02-26",
      },
      {
        author: "Lydia Long",
        rating: 5,
        comment: "Parent born fine plan act result.",
        date: "2024-02-19",
      },
      {
        author: "Sharon Perez DVM",
        rating: 2,
        comment: "School film first continue guess field.",
        date: "2024-02-13",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "My fly never task.",
        answer: "Tree trade Republican walk fill factor gas.",
        date: "2024-02-16",
      },
      {
        question: "Night exactly on.",
        answer: "Office many themselves husband year box true.",
        date: "2024-01-16",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 83,
    name: "Ürün 83",
    category: "Elektronik",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 993.33,
    brand: "Marka ",
    stock: 37,
    ratings: {
      average: 1.8,
      count: 931,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "APS-C",
      resolution: "31MP",
      videoResolution: "4K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: false,
        bluetooth: true,
        gps: false,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "AA",
        life: "900 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "882g",
        dimensions: "119 x 83 x 58 mm",
        color: "Kırmızı",
      },
    },
    accessories: ["Yedek Batarya", "Lens Temizleme Kiti", "Filtre Kitleri"],
    warranty: "2 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 30,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "3-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["Kredi Kartı", "Banka Havalesi", "Kripto Para"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Austin Sanchez",
        rating: 2,
        comment: "Talk security hold new rate.",
        date: "2024-01-25",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "May wear there relate himself describe.",
        answer: "Music likely expert time particularly structure camera.",
        date: "2024-03-14",
      },
      {
        question: "Lead artist owner continue source without.",
        answer: "Animal push example design.",
        date: "2024-02-12",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 84,
    name: "Ürün 84",
    category: "Ev & Yaşam",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 4742.91,
    brand: "Marka ",
    stock: 42,
    ratings: {
      average: 3.2,
      count: 205,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Full Frame",
      resolution: "36MP",
      videoResolution: "1080p",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: false,
        bluetooth: false,
        gps: false,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "AA",
        life: "887 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "689g",
        dimensions: "135 x 62 x 90 mm",
        color: "Kırmızı",
      },
    },
    accessories: [
      "Yedek Batarya",
      "Lens Temizleme Kiti",
      "Filtre Kitleri",
      "Tripod",
    ],
    warranty: "3 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 30,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "5-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["EFT", "Kapıda Ödeme", "Kripto Para"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Brandon Jones",
        rating: 2,
        comment: "Ability commercial even century expect.",
        date: "2024-01-26",
      },
      {
        author: "Misty Franklin",
        rating: 5,
        comment: "Adult begin source note world.",
        date: "2024-03-18",
      },
      {
        author: "Lisa Parsons",
        rating: 4,
        comment: "Score program get level class stay.",
        date: "2024-01-20",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Most point eye member positive.",
        answer: "Statement soldier indicate close support.",
        date: "2024-02-14",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 85,
    name: "Ürün 85",
    category: "Elektronik",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 4212.83,
    brand: "Marka ",
    stock: 61,
    ratings: {
      average: 2.9,
      count: 436,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Micro Four Thirds",
      resolution: "32MP",
      videoResolution: "4K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: true,
        bluetooth: false,
        gps: false,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "Li-ion",
        life: "890 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "1274g",
        dimensions: "136 x 62 x 52 mm",
        color: "Siyah",
      },
    },
    accessories: ["Filtre Kitleri", "Lens Temizleme Kiti"],
    warranty: "3 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 30,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "5-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["Kripto Para", "Kredi Kartı", "Kapıda Ödeme"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Ann Vaughn",
        rating: 4,
        comment: "Process professor foreign down foot.",
        date: "2024-01-24",
      },
      {
        author: "Catherine Taylor",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "Education area event.",
        date: "2024-02-07",
      },
      {
        author: "Tiffany Johnson",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Pick see already seem return phone.",
        date: "2024-03-07",
      },
      {
        author: "Damon Taylor",
        rating: 2,
        comment: "During resource recognize politics.",
        date: "2024-02-10",
      },
      {
        author: "Richard Cortez",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "West run hospital inside wear sing exist despite.",
        date: "2024-01-30",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Network generation own first teach line mention.",
        answer: "Return effort ready early produce wait decision outside.",
        date: "2024-03-14",
      },
      {
        question: "Few color there fact beyond.",
        answer: "Inside cut probably middle place.",
        date: "2024-01-30",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 86,
    name: "Ürün 86",
    category: "Kişisel Bakım",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 4018.97,
    brand: "Marka ",
    stock: 40,
    ratings: {
      average: 1.6,
      count: 584,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Full Frame",
      resolution: "58MP",
      videoResolution: "1080p",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: false,
        bluetooth: false,
        gps: false,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "Li-ion",
        life: "786 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "618g",
        dimensions: "142 x 65 x 70 mm",
        color: "Kırmızı",
      },
    },
    accessories: [
      "Yedek Batarya",
      "Lens Temizleme Kiti",
      "Tripod",
      "Taşıma Çantası",
    ],
    warranty: "3 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 15,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "2-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: [
      "Kapıda Ödeme",
      "EFT",
      "Kripto Para",
      "Banka Havalesi",
      "Kredi Kartı",
    ],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Jamie Maxwell",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "Song live owner operation risk four against.",
        date: "2024-01-07",
      },
      {
        author: "Laura Terry MD",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Free fill event toward create door social.",
        date: "2024-02-18",
      },
      {
        author: "Holly Krause",
        rating: 5,
        comment: "Week huge guess job focus message around.",
        date: "2024-03-18",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Book exist use take one change tell.",
        answer: "Something throughout specific move.",
        date: "2024-01-09",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 87,
    name: "Ürün 87",
    category: "Elektronik",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 2140.66,
    brand: "Marka ",
    stock: 77,
    ratings: {
      average: 3.9,
      count: 83,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "APS-C",
      resolution: "14MP",
      videoResolution: "1080p",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: true,
        bluetooth: false,
        gps: false,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "Li-ion",
        life: "413 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "588g",
        dimensions: "146 x 85 x 45 mm",
        color: "Siyah",
      },
    },
    accessories: ["Yedek Batarya"],
    warranty: "3 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 60,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "1-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["EFT", "Banka Havalesi"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Joanne Lawson",
        rating: 5,
        comment: "Step challenge this change assume long no.",
        date: "2024-02-07",
      },
      {
        author: "Henry Meyer",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "Involve quite into how improve keep rich.",
        date: "2024-02-15",
      },
      {
        author: "John Bradley",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Class wind race whatever three hold.",
        date: "2024-01-31",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Almost thank song able foreign.",
        answer: "Staff hit phone build prepare prove.",
        date: "2024-01-04",
      },
      {
        question: "Agent leader like indicate nation country senior.",
        answer: "Democrat rest truth market debate win.",
        date: "2024-03-12",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 88,
    name: "Ürün 88",
    category: "Elektronik",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 3848.69,
    brand: "Marka ",
    stock: 12,
    ratings: {
      average: 1.5,
      count: 32,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "APS-C",
      resolution: "30MP",
      videoResolution: "4K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: false,
        bluetooth: false,
        gps: false,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "Li-ion",
        life: "560 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "1050g",
        dimensions: "146 x 102 x 30 mm",
        color: "Kırmızı",
      },
    },
    accessories: [
      "Filtre Kitleri",
      "Lens Temizleme Kiti",
      "Yedek Batarya",
      "Taşıma Çantası",
      "Tripod",
    ],
    warranty: "3 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 15,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "2-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["EFT", "Banka Havalesi"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Deborah Tucker",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "Decade professor everyone find store which player goal.",
        date: "2024-01-07",
      },
      {
        author: "Gavin Mccoy",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Television true agency hour surface leg lawyer pattern.",
        date: "2024-02-03",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Leg yeah point card operation south.",
        answer: "None our statement computer kitchen lose.",
        date: "2024-01-10",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 89,
    name: "Ürün 89",
    category: "Kişisel Bakım",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 775.23,
    brand: "Marka ",
    stock: 59,
    ratings: {
      average: 4.7,
      count: 935,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Micro Four Thirds",
      resolution: "14MP",
      videoResolution: "8K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: true,
        bluetooth: false,
        gps: false,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "AA",
        life: "726 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "1100g",
        dimensions: "118 x 124 x 47 mm",
        color: "Siyah",
      },
    },
    accessories: ["Tripod", "Yedek Batarya", "Lens Temizleme Kiti"],
    warranty: "3 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 15,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "3-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["Banka Havalesi", "Kripto Para", "Kredi Kartı"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Dawn Garcia",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "Feel nature explain style.",
        date: "2024-01-14",
      },
      {
        author: "Alicia Thompson",
        rating: 2,
        comment: "Idea mind whole administration window base measure.",
        date: "2024-02-09",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Sell sound represent.",
        answer: "Answer still learn enjoy share form.",
        date: "2024-02-27",
      },
      {
        question: "Work church seat himself.",
        answer: "So teacher position arrive approach similar production.",
        date: "2024-03-20",
      },
      {
        question: "Body network peace provide series.",
        answer: "Assume each daughter maybe.",
        date: "2024-02-21",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 90,
    name: "Ürün 90",
    category: "Kişisel Bakım",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 933.57,
    brand: "Marka ",
    stock: 15,
    ratings: {
      average: 3.9,
      count: 978,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Micro Four Thirds",
      resolution: "40MP",
      videoResolution: "4K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: false,
        bluetooth: true,
        gps: false,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "Li-ion",
        life: "959 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "1157g",
        dimensions: "144 x 73 x 66 mm",
        color: "Mavi",
      },
    },
    accessories: ["Filtre Kitleri", "Lens Temizleme Kiti", "Yedek Batarya"],
    warranty: "2 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 30,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "1-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["Banka Havalesi", "Kripto Para", "EFT", "Kapıda Ödeme"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Alison Turner",
        rating: 2,
        comment: "East pass house.",
        date: "2024-01-11",
      },
      {
        author: "Timothy Monroe",
        rating: 4,
        comment: "Analysis from prevent plant name work.",
        date: "2024-02-28",
      },
      {
        author: "Stephanie Taylor",
        rating: 5,
        comment: "Southern business skill with camera participant hot.",
        date: "2024-02-13",
      },
      {
        author: "Daniel Baker",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Rate authority whole part easy around memory southern.",
        date: "2024-01-11",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Mouth trade collection night.",
        answer: "Trip over its high.",
        date: "2024-01-23",
      },
      {
        question: "Point personal letter entire.",
        answer: "Voice social anyone thank have house during.",
        date: "2024-02-10",
      },
      {
        question: "Send style reduce nor apply.",
        answer:
          "Director officer increase tough population authority front south.",
        date: "2024-03-02",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 91,
    name: "Ürün 91",
    category: "Elektronik",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 4349.72,
    brand: "Marka ",
    stock: 52,
    ratings: {
      average: 4.2,
      count: 535,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Micro Four Thirds",
      resolution: "40MP",
      videoResolution: "1080p",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: true,
        bluetooth: true,
        gps: false,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "AA",
        life: "382 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "668g",
        dimensions: "136 x 66 x 99 mm",
        color: "Gri",
      },
    },
    accessories: ["Filtre Kitleri"],
    warranty: "3 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 60,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "5-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["Banka Havalesi"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Mary Washington",
        rating: 2,
        comment: "Real health too debate.",
        date: "2024-03-21",
      },
      {
        author: "Megan Lopez",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Hundred difference determine.",
        date: "2024-03-09",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Worker sing step here dinner.",
        answer: "Loss whether fight these.",
        date: "2024-01-14",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 92,
    name: "Ürün 92",
    category: "Kişisel Bakım",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 3805.49,
    brand: "Marka ",
    stock: 88,
    ratings: {
      average: 3.8,
      count: 751,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "APS-C",
      resolution: "48MP",
      videoResolution: "8K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: true,
        bluetooth: true,
        gps: true,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "Li-ion",
        life: "498 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "1125g",
        dimensions: "101 x 113 x 30 mm",
        color: "Siyah",
      },
    },
    accessories: [
      "Taşıma Çantası",
      "Lens Temizleme Kiti",
      "Tripod",
      "Yedek Batarya",
    ],
    warranty: "1 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 60,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "5-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: [
      "Kapıda Ödeme",
      "Banka Havalesi",
      "Kredi Kartı",
      "Kripto Para",
      "EFT",
    ],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Christine Fisher",
        rating: 2,
        comment: "Economic back next talk cup fear character.",
        date: "2024-01-20",
      },
      {
        author: "Misty Abbott",
        rating: 4,
        comment: "Relate series executive cost offer happy.",
        date: "2024-03-23",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Very let former resource wind rock.",
        answer: "Become score near.",
        date: "2024-03-11",
      },
      {
        question: "Rule physical research start allow their.",
        answer: "Discuss green song.",
        date: "2024-03-17",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 93,
    name: "Ürün 93",
    category: "Elektronik",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 225.88,
    brand: "Marka ",
    stock: 39,
    ratings: {
      average: 2.7,
      count: 923,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "APS-C",
      resolution: "41MP",
      videoResolution: "8K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: false,
        bluetooth: true,
        gps: true,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "AA",
        life: "441 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "1090g",
        dimensions: "117 x 97 x 35 mm",
        color: "Kırmızı",
      },
    },
    accessories: ["Lens Temizleme Kiti", "Filtre Kitleri", "Yedek Batarya"],
    warranty: "2 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 60,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "5-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["Kripto Para", "EFT", "Kredi Kartı"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Jessica Mckenzie",
        rating: 5,
        comment: "Office story laugh avoid night.",
        date: "2024-02-20",
      },
      {
        author: "Megan Price",
        rating: 4,
        comment: "Discuss present notice everyone.",
        date: "2024-01-08",
      },
      {
        author: "Andrea Sheppard",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "Series will candidate every.",
        date: "2024-03-11",
      },
      {
        author: "Andrew Rice",
        rating: 2,
        comment: "Buy sign visit perform.",
        date: "2024-01-06",
      },
      {
        author: "Stephanie Sanchez",
        rating: 2,
        comment: "Audience use prevent economic accept economy common.",
        date: "2024-02-28",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Down design training though nation.",
        answer: "National law card chair use up staff.",
        date: "2024-03-02",
      },
      {
        question: "Build charge successful collection.",
        answer: "Performance raise responsibility parent.",
        date: "2024-02-09",
      },
      {
        question: "Result protect raise total.",
        answer: "Store value remember.",
        date: "2024-01-28",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 94,
    name: "Ürün 94",
    category: "Kişisel Bakım",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 1428.82,
    brand: "Marka ",
    stock: 24,
    ratings: {
      average: 3.6,
      count: 878,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Full Frame",
      resolution: "12MP",
      videoResolution: "4K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: false,
        bluetooth: false,
        gps: false,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "AA",
        life: "663 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "561g",
        dimensions: "122 x 71 x 36 mm",
        color: "Mavi",
      },
    },
    accessories: ["Lens Temizleme Kiti", "Ekstra Lens", "Yedek Batarya"],
    warranty: "3 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 15,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "5-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["Kripto Para", "Banka Havalesi", "Kredi Kartı", "EFT"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Lisa Nguyen DVM",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "And threat around yet oil husband deep.",
        date: "2024-03-22",
      },
      {
        author: "Eric Young",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "Around feeling from of director become.",
        date: "2024-01-27",
      },
      {
        author: "Kevin Henderson",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Well can day way military themselves.",
        date: "2024-02-04",
      },
      {
        author: "Ronald Garrett",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Summer before evidence avoid.",
        date: "2024-02-06",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Chair offer court ok despite.",
        answer: "Thousand really good clear family down nothing great.",
        date: "2024-03-11",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 95,
    name: "Ürün 95",
    category: "Kişisel Bakım",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 2462.94,
    brand: "Marka ",
    stock: 62,
    ratings: {
      average: 1.5,
      count: 868,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Micro Four Thirds",
      resolution: "36MP",
      videoResolution: "1080p",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: true,
        bluetooth: true,
        gps: true,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "AA",
        life: "621 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "736g",
        dimensions: "126 x 108 x 61 mm",
        color: "Gri",
      },
    },
    accessories: [
      "Tripod",
      "Taşıma Çantası",
      "Yedek Batarya",
      "Lens Temizleme Kiti",
      "Filtre Kitleri",
      "Ekstra Lens",
    ],
    warranty: "1 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 15,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "1-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["Kapıda Ödeme", "Kredi Kartı", "Banka Havalesi"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Matthew Mullins",
        rating: 5,
        comment: "Half however establish buy else simple later.",
        date: "2024-01-19",
      },
      {
        author: "Elizabeth Oneal",
        rating: 4,
        comment: "Fast who economic better.",
        date: "2024-01-19",
      },
      {
        author: "Ryan Baxter",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "Right movie policy wait.",
        date: "2024-01-19",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Soon child thought day.",
        answer: "Against along benefit reach role whom make idea.",
        date: "2024-03-25",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 96,
    name: "Ürün 96",
    category: "Ev & Yaşam",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 1480.97,
    brand: "Marka  ",
    stock: 81,
    ratings: {
      average: 4.9,
      count: 439,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Micro Four Thirds",
      resolution: "29MP",
      videoResolution: "8K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: false,
        bluetooth: false,
        gps: false,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "AA",
        life: "630 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "866g",
        dimensions: "150 x 118 x 33 mm",
        color: "Kırmızı",
      },
    },
    accessories: ["Tripod", "Lens Temizleme Kiti", "Taşıma Çantası"],
    warranty: "3 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 30,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "7-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["Kripto Para"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Linda Williams",
        rating: 2,
        comment: "General require item most knowledge discuss person.",
        date: "2024-03-08",
      },
      {
        author: "Eric Moore",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "Operation perhaps keep thousand range end newspaper.",
        date: "2024-01-01",
      },
      {
        author: "Joel Craig",
        rating: 2,
        comment: "Tax nothing your.",
        date: "2024-02-14",
      },
      {
        author: "Michael Castillo",
        rating: 4,
        comment: "Law discussion half others ready person two.",
        date: "2024-01-07",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Visit camera may many program.",
        answer: "Mother hard difficult onto girl up lay.",
        date: "2024-03-02",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 97,
    name: "Ürün 97",
    category: "Elektronik",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 4284.73,
    brand: "Marka ¡",
    stock: 27,
    ratings: {
      average: 2.8,
      count: 47,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Full Frame",
      resolution: "55MP",
      videoResolution: "1080p",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: false,
        bluetooth: false,
        gps: false,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "AA",
        life: "388 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "344g",
        dimensions: "141 x 125 x 69 mm",
        color: "Gri",
      },
    },
    accessories: [
      "Yedek Batarya",
      "Filtre Kitleri",
      "Taşıma Çantası",
      "Ekstra Lens",
      "Tripod",
    ],
    warranty: "3 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 30,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "5-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["Kredi Kartı", "Kripto Para"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Rhonda White",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "Between house spring top various most.",
        date: "2024-03-16",
      },
      {
        author: "Margaret Martin",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "Prevent magazine low tend choice.",
        date: "2024-01-21",
      },
      {
        author: "Jeanne Gallagher",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "Adult wonder author whose.",
        date: "2024-02-02",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Away worry hand have dark top.",
        answer: "Open walk rather add TV page.",
        date: "2024-02-24",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 98,
    name: "Ürün 98",
    category: "Ev & Yaşam",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 1913.91,
    brand: "Marka ¢",
    stock: 88,
    ratings: {
      average: 2.7,
      count: 304,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "Full Frame",
      resolution: "40MP",
      videoResolution: "1080p",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: true,
        bluetooth: true,
        gps: false,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "AA",
        life: "338 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "1064g",
        dimensions: "127 x 63 x 84 mm",
        color: "Mavi",
      },
    },
    accessories: [
      "Taşıma Çantası",
      "Yedek Batarya",
      "Tripod",
      "Lens Temizleme Kiti",
    ],
    warranty: "2 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 30,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "7-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["Kredi Kartı", "Kapıda Ödeme"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "John Flores",
        rating: 2,
        comment: "Television play whatever star other realize dinner.",
        date: "2024-03-12",
      },
      {
        author: "Danielle Burton",
        rating: 4,
        comment: "Gas source significant simple simply.",
        date: "2024-02-26",
      },
      {
        author: "Stephanie Howard",
        rating: 2,
        comment: "Special medical many plant student indeed star.",
        date: "2024-03-19",
      },
      {
        author: "Christopher Strong",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "Notice pay husband worker.",
        date: "2024-03-08",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Report system he foot.",
        answer: "Lot base which value.",
        date: "2024-02-18",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 99,
    name: "Ürün 99",
    category: "Elektronik",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 3498.02,
    brand: "Marka £",
    stock: 69,
    ratings: {
      average: 1.8,
      count: 920,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "APS-C",
      resolution: "48MP",
      videoResolution: "8K",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: true,
        bluetooth: false,
        gps: true,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "Li-ion",
        life: "700 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "467g",
        dimensions: "142 x 79 x 77 mm",
        color: "Siyah",
      },
    },
    accessories: [
      "Taşıma Çantası",
      "Filtre Kitleri",
      "Tripod",
      "Lens Temizleme Kiti",
    ],
    warranty: "2 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 15,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "2-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: ["Banka Havalesi", "Kripto Para"],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Theresa Thomas",
        rating: 2,
        comment: "Pull under example shoulder even.",
        date: "2024-01-21",
      },
      {
        author: "Robert Miller",
        rating: 4,
        comment: "Option manager structure toward care talk.",
        date: "2024-02-11",
      },
      {
        author: "Diane Fuller",
        rating: 1,
        comment: "Lawyer example national land successful drive.",
        date: "2024-02-24",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Identify well feeling design.",
        answer: "Degree popular all speak court wonder generation.",
        date: "2024-02-01",
      },
      {
        question: "Customer young past system seem can.",
        answer: "Prevent recent answer.",
        date: "2024-02-07",
      },
      {
        question: "Evening unit event little someone.",
        answer: "Expert discuss center young allow election rest but.",
        date: "2024-02-02",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 100,
    name: "Ürün 100",
    category: "Ev & Yaşam",
    subcategory: "Kamera & Fotoğraf",
    price: 4937.91,
    brand: "Marka ¤",
    stock: 17,
    ratings: {
      average: 1.7,
      count: 541,
    },
    features: {
      sensor: "APS-C",
      resolution: "42MP",
      videoResolution: "1080p",
      connectivity: {
        wifi: true,
        bluetooth: false,
        gps: true,
      },
      battery: {
        type: "AA",
        life: "665 shots",
      },
      physical: {
        weight: "891g",
        dimensions: "147 x 110 x 47 mm",
        color: "Mavi",
      },
    },
    accessories: ["Lens Temizleme Kiti", "Taşıma Çantası", "Ekstra Lens"],
    warranty: "3 Yıl",
    returnPolicy: {
      days: 30,
      condition: "İade için ürünün zarar görmemiş olması gerekir",
    },
    shipping: {
      type: "Ücretsiz",
      duration: "5-5 iş günü",
    },
    paymentOptions: [
      "Kredi Kartı",
      "Banka Havalesi",
      "Kripto Para",
      "EFT",
      "Kapıda Ödeme",
    ],
    reviews: [
      {
        author: "Samuel Stark",
        rating: 2,
        comment: "Increase different cup stay food most whose song.",
        date: "2024-03-19",
      },
      {
        author: "Juan Soto",
        rating: 3,
        comment: "Try win visit might feel kid traditional.",
        date: "2024-01-15",
      },
      {
        author: "Veronica Day",
        rating: 5,
        comment: "Strategy everyone career store team.",
        date: "2024-02-04",
      },
      {
        author: "Jared Crosby",
        rating: 2,
        comment: "Meet budget garden sea.",
        date: "2024-02-24",
      },
    ],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Employee image style defense value focus without.",
        answer: "Executive feeling project expert able best.",
        date: "2024-02-25",
      },
      {
        question: "The agency strategy child leader.",
        answer: "After forward finish range could way.",
        date: "2024-02-16",
      },
    ],
  },
];
